a bad time and at that point that's like
that's a hypothetically that's like that's
like essentially you know we talk about
extinction level events i think in our life
in in the in the history of life on the planet
there have been like four extinction level events
that's like that's another that's an
extinction level event you know what i mean
like a super volcano on the planet
that's an extinction level event
like a giant another giant asteroid hitting the
planet that's an extinction level event you know
like there's a lot of stuff that like has to kind
of go right even if you're doing all the right
things to kind of try to make the jump from like a
type 1 to a type 2 civilization you know yeah it's
it's my [ __ ] it's a lot i've
never thought about moving a star
so it's a novel idea like um like i mean like
i said like that's one way essentially like
you essentially keep the power source with
you right it's like going on the plane with
your batteries you know i mean i feel like you
don't ever you just make artificial life though
so that that's the thing right
with to some extent like um
this is what i was talking a little bit about the
relativity of it right so let's say we're talking
about the distances between stars right maybe
you go maybe like a 20 at the speed of light so
if you're trying to get to an object that's like
four light years away it'll take you like 80 years
right assuming you can go that fast um the
perception of time for the people on that ship
will be substantially less it won't feel like 80
years to you it might only feel like 80 years you
right so like the big thing being was like you
know when gps was the big example of it right
when they put the first gps satellites in
orbit all of their times were wrong against
the times on the ground and it's because
satellites move fast enough that they're
going to fall back a few split seconds
behind with the clocks on the ground to
that's like relativistic time it basically
that's actually how they prove that like
that part of einstein's theory about time being
relative that was how they proved it was actually
the gps satellites so it's a very simple
very similar idea effectively where
if you were going fast enough in a rocket ship
yeah for us sitting at earth waiting be like man i
hope jim makes it to that you know to that star i
won't be alive to see it but yeah that'll be cool
you know for jim it might only be like 30
years whereas for you and i it would be 80
because his time would have slowed his
relative time would have slowed down
right you know it's like it's a very
it's a very strange thing that that
includes the process of aging all of that but
that has its limits too because you only hit
you have your your mass is also
correlated to your speed correct so
you can't it's the same reason you can't go
with the speed of light right because it's like
you got to be massless correct exactly it'd be
like a photon right you have to be something
that essentially that is pure energy which is why
for us to actually defy or even reach the speed of
light you'd have to find some kind of a loophole
right the math doesn't allow it i mean it's
a stellar like a a true hyperdrive is something
that i think is theoretically possible
it's just like god knows how long it would be for
something like that to happen and like the amount
of scientific hurdles you have to overcome like
i'm a big apollo 13 guy so i always kind of think
about like when they had that disaster when they
were trying to go to the moon the amount of steps
it took for those pilot for those astronauts to
make their way home right if any one of those
steps fail they don't make it that's the end right
honestly i don't know apollo 13. that's crazy
could you could you enlighten me
so so apollo 11 right that's actually the first
man touchdown on the moon they actually reached
the moon and yet knee alarms strong you
know buzz like one small step before nine
right everybody's height yeah
that's 11. so apollo 13 comes up
people are excited we're going
backwards it's a fake one right
well 11 the one they say that was
filmed in the in the in the movie
a lot at mgm or something oh right now
yeah no so there so 13 happens right so
if you haven't seen it i i i i i remember
hollywood if you haven't seen it i highly
recommend the tom hanks movie i mean
there's a couple of good movies about
but like tom hanks apollo 13. i think it is
like the quintessential like human ingenuity
like i mean it's it's it's a great phenomenal
movie it's even more phenomenal story but