it is the game that paralyzes the world the one
that can decide a champion the one that
can change the leader good evening
all of this is the great classic of
spanish football real madrid-fc barcelona
two styles two teams two trenches
but the same objective wants to win the
championship  from league one riding the wave
of the champions the other wanting to
overcome the fall in the same tournament
some of the best players in the
world on the pitch and a
brilliant night for the
stars to shine at the santiago
bernabéu stadium we
present the team that  is going to tell about
this game in the league tv rubén de la
red very good hello very good night
albert luque good night first
reflection that his assets the same the
head great
game great game the league a game in the santiago bernabéu full
atmosphere of luxury the best game that
we can see today for me and above
all with the importance of knowing that
if real madrid wins they
would practically have the league in their hands at v  Well,
if I totally agree with Rubén, it's
good night. I think that Madrid
can sentence the league. I think that on the
part of Barça we are going to see the best
version of FC.Barcelona. When they
are at the limit, it is
when the expensive
scenario is a  scenario that he loves
fc barcelona he loves giving surprises
in this stadium and I think it
will be very difficult for madrid to win it
fc.barcelona both teams come out onto the
pitch very quickly
proper names of whoever expected him to
shine today  the bernabéu
well it is clear that cristiano ronaldo is
the benchmark for real madrid
especially the goalscoring aspect but well I
hope
we will see an important game in which
the midfield is to play
the important part
with luka modric who dominates
the game
yes from the usual barça of
all in an offensive facet
we are going to expect great and from time to
time it may be
lately he is not appearing in his
best mom  ent but in these stadiums right
now dad
both messi and suárez is all praise
that barça has in attack and we will
see if they appear in the health of the
players of the two teams sing to
the santiago bernabéu stadium or the anthem of
the white team the anthem  of the centenary
we passed the line-up of real madrid
with rubén de la red this is the eleven of
the white team that you record in the frame
four behind carvajal
lateral sergio ramos rancho couple of
central defenders in front the anchor the axis
of the team is casemiro
accompanied by luka modric  and by toni
kross above, cristiano
ronaldo karim benzema gareth bale returns to the bbc the
starting team of real madrid and not
with the defense where nacho
[Music]
you are playing good games and being
the starter to stop and pp are
injured and estonia maybe there can be
if they were fine any doubt
but otherwise
[Music]
in the idea that you decide where
gareth bale is not the best at his
best his best  r way of life that
vision but he has the confidence of the
coach we review 11 of fc barcelona
with albert luque ter stegen in
goal sergi roberto right lane
jordi alba in the left gerard piqué
samuel a marmoset couple of central
defenders sergio Busquets will be barça's beacon
with  ivan rakitic andrés iniesta the
attacking trio paco alcácer luís suárez free
of the month and so for barça
luxury defense the best defense i
think luis enrique can jump in this
match in midfield i
totally agree also with Busquets rakitic
and iniesta  I think he is the center of the
field with a higher level than the one he has
in this squad and above because one can
not count on Neymar, he cannot
play in the mls due to cancer he has
another game to show that we are going to
see if he is  at the level of a match like
these
I think it is to be a great team with a
lot of level
in a match like this in a match of
this level
at this point the person pr  otagonist
in the prize of the match the honorary kick-off
that
Sergio García is going to perform the great winner a short time ago
from Augusta's master's degree it was a
tremendous prize for a Sergio García
who
[Applause]
with this you the best Spanish golfer for
me a great Real Madrid player also  I like
football a lot, good good people,
I have deserved this kick-off
that so many successes accompany us in
the Spanish goal and above all because the
match in a Madrid-Barça that is the best that
remains of the kick-off and we must
also mention  to the referee who is a
great referee el canario
hernández hernández and to ask maybe he has gained
a little understanding because surely
someone will do what he makes
his decisions in today's game that
will start with the ball for real
madrid that will be on the left  from their
screens to the right
at fc barcelona- the atmosphere is
huge at the bernabéu
say in game
everything is ready for the
classic to start bring out karim benzema
in u  second we are going to have football
the game that paralyzes the world that
we have seen before in new york in
so many places they are going to continue the
classic
[Applause]
for toni kross training for luka
modric first position for real
madrid
estevez transaction has been made  first
position for real madrid nacho with
sergio ramos barça is waiting for the moment
because they don't press too high the first
mistake made
by sergio ramos yes what i had
said about it is that barça is going to
play a 4-3-3 in attack and it's the  system that
he likes the most took place in ce lona but in
defense we are going to see how andrés iniesta
is to put a little more into the midfield
and cancer cancer is going to do a little
more defensive work playing with a
4-4-2 leaving in  the point of attack
both suárez and leo messi play real
madrid that croatian luka modric
[Applause
] misses the deflected ball in that
deep ball attempt
germany today we see luis enrique for a
quiet moment in his  u bench
the fc barcelona coach who returns, as you
well know, to one of the places where he
spent his professional career as
a real madrid player
head tití divided ball that wins
casemiro fight luka modric get to
action on andrés iniesta the camera
casemiro da la  advantage
hernández hernández sergio ramos- barça field
delivery for marcelo karim benzema is coming
playing with casemiro playing for sergio
ramos
looking for the ball for what
christian
the controversial minute and a half
is about samuel against you
madrid ep
penalty restriction
[Applause]
we will wait for a repetition  between
gareth bale for toni kroos this with
casemiro casemiro looking for marcelo
goal ball
[Applause]
the white team the match and here is
the image between christian ronaldo
and samuel
with both legs first with the
right or the left very clear penalty
in favor of  real madrid well I
think a joke made me see myself a little and
there is a Christian who gives him a little
cristian Cristiano's control of
anticipating brother and when he sees that
the ball does not arrive he drops I think
there is contact but not for it to fall to the
ground
sorry he
put his club foot in a marmoset in the
race against Cristiano Ronaldo how
the team started  target of increase
attacking the zinc and identity team
barça lacks the ball, which is their
work tool and they still have
n't seen it in these first few seconds
luka modric stuck on the lime steals
andrés iniesta ball down
cancer tried to get out  barça luis
suárez on the run against the hook
providing the madrid central defender modric
for toni kross open to the right
handing over to luka modric delaying
sergio ramos' position
barça is a bit retracted in
these first moments
marcelo plays with gareth bale he would
delay sergio  Ramos- Cavero sends towards the
sea and Carvajal heads to the right,
delaying for Cristiano Ronaldo,
but the one who heads because he follows the
attack  that from real madrid luka modric danny
carvajal
carvajal with an adult mother and fear in the
center
[Applause]
that has come out very strong, very dominant,
generating danger at times in fc
barcelona that does not leave his own area
not here we have repeated it again
first he hits him  the right leg
arriving late is anticipated very well
sad no ronaldo and then with the
left for me it is a penalty and
barça has to make some adjustments in
this left wing to cancer has to
be aware of carvajal more than
carbonell
because the madridista carrying  the rhythm
of the game
carbajales a real dagger down this
right wing and he will need a
little more help from jordi alba
because these changes of fire are
surprising fc barcelona a lot the ball does
not last at all barça attacks
real madrid marcelo  colliding with
sergi roberto wide ball for the
white team zinedine zidane leaves his bench
to give instructions from the
french coach continues  on attack
madrid gareth bale puts his foot in sergi
Busquets robs the azulgrana team
for andrés iniesta iniesta than the
stone under super intense pressure from realmadrid
but receives the first
ball of the game leo messi has the
whole lane open jordi alba prefers to
stop and deliver  for the argentinian
and he is with leo messi barça wants to slow him down
and
see if barça as they are watching
the game especially with the intensity
that has come from real madrid what he
wants is not to lose the ball having
in his  his position and then look
for attacking moves later because
real madrid comes out the counter is coming
benzema benzema christian's career
christian ronaldo and gerard piqué reaches
the portuguese christian's backheel
can shoot with the left
madrid's attack
two minutes the shot  by Cristiano
Ronaldo, very focused on this occasion, for
sure, ter Stegen caught
very well, Real Madrid went on the
counterattack, gaining space  that they
are leaving the ball behind them and
a real madrid that has come out from the
first minute to take the initiative in
the game to put that pressure on portugal
when they also have
to play with them for the points they
have in their favor  in the standings and
especially on occasions i don't think
that if madrid gets ahead
mentally they will win a lot
now barça attacks in the absolutely
opposite style real madrid wants to
speed it up barça wants to guide him
jordi plays al
suárez
right nacho  to cut it is not worth it and
despite the move because the
uruguayan had been offside
here we are going to see him the center of jordi
spoke to the movement of luis suárez and it
seems to me that there is no heart our
bouquets section is online
and I think  how good we have seen that luis
suárez is 'the one in legal position and first
mistake of the linesman possession for the
white team looks for marcelo the weak ball
because here we will also have to see  the
repetition in that career of the player from
cardiff
deep ball by marcelo in realmadrid
mixing the game short ball long ball
that is gareth bale's exit i like it
now
that no
how nice the game is no grave
the classic started at the height of
what  than expected let's hope they
continue like this for at least the
first 45 minutes if we can enjoy
the game as we are doing
at the front of the area 10 hernández
hernández
is on the ground on 1 he has not recovered the
throw-in for the team  from luis
enrique and there he is complaining about the hit
luis suárez at the front of the area
when he was trying to maneuver against carlos
enrique casemiro he controls himself well he wants to
turn and there it is seen that there is a contact
that I know that javi suárez but I think
there is casimiro anticipates  well he
takes the ball well and well for me they were
hernández this time it was not
right
[Music]
with maximum intensity and casemiro recovers the
ball for marcelo m  arcelo
turns hand over to nacho this with danny
carvajal palmas at the santiago
bernabeú stadium match 8 the classic
underway
0-0 at the moment on the scoreboard luka
modric leaves it for nacho hands over this
to sergio ramos
andalusian defense
to win
toni kroos o manda  he sends the ball to the german
for luka modric i entered from the
right profile he plays with karim benzema
this one for luca modric danny carvajal
open looks for the long ball breaks
christian
to come back
providential in the court that good one a
marmoset me and barça have to be very
aware of  Cristiano I see him very
focused all the time looking for
in-depth value
and it is one of those games that Cristiano
wants to win of all and of
those you want to see in these last
days more motivated and roberto for
samuel to you and starting the game
barça a marmoset stepping on the ball delivery
for sergio Busquets here is the beacon
of barça the mind for leo messi changes
the rhythm in argentina
to cancer  with ivan rakitic he served the
left where he has a lot of space
jordi alba leo messi in the front he loses
control a little bit but he
can touch it for Busquets search he doesn't
even threaten to look for the
preferred shot for andrés iniesta iniesta's shot
capo nacho kick off  band
for barça these six players who
are intimidated by the departure of real
madrid it
is clear that iniesta and leo messi are
the players with the most personality they are
the players who want the ball who
are having the most daring delivery
we have seen other players who
prefer to keep that  ball play
safer play backwards from there fc
barcelona has to be careful with
those values ​​that went backwards
luckily with the sensation that it can give
is gradually regaining control
sergi roberto delays
gerard piqué's slip that comes from the  Pressure from
Karim Benzema, Sergio Busquets playing
with Andres Iniesta, Ivan Rakitic returns it
between the lines.  s leo messi puts in
for jordi alba he returns centrally he
faces luis suárez to look for the
shot
he went to the right to
luis suárez's shot
make the barça in the game without a
very good move by fc
barcelona and jordi alba's great internal
everyone was expecting a paid pass we had to
do that he came in to finish off
but that day I had seen
luis suárez very well on the edge of the area that
he did very well with quick control
with a very good shot because he was going to
grass level that if they had taken the
goal would have put
the base in many difficulties
10 minutes of the game in the Clásico
against Madrid 0 fc barcelona 0 ball for
zinedine zidane's team sergio abramos hands over
to marcelo
ramos luis suárez squeezes him he plays with nacho
the closeness of leo messi nacho to
danny carvajal the perfect inward cut
of the winger from leganés plays with
casemiro's songbook changing
but it is the first one that stayed
with him  against the brazilian
rakitic another one slips and there is the
croat rakitic managing the leather very
pressured he has to play with marc
andre ter stegen
alemany you will not have too much problem
to play with the foot there is a marmoset with
jordi alba
deepening enough the
barça side that is  itches and with gareth bale
ball for sergio Busquets he gives himself
to leo messi- appearing a lot
inside argentinian he wants to leave
casemiro there he was
if messi goes back and card to go
after cancer to the first yellow card of the
game he left all the  barça the pressure
casemiro
booked at the 11th game yes because let's
see it's like the saying is the first in the
absence of almost less but at no
time does he have the chance to touch the
ball I think that there he comes out a little
angry because of the dribbling he did  leo
messi and there is a bit that it is already
impossible for him to get in contact with the
ball entered from behind and for my
yellow card very well taken by
hernández hernánde  z
a very clear yellow card and also
very stupid on the part of cashmere
because he did not get to that play at any
time and especially since minutes 10
minutes 11 having a yellow card is
as important for balance as it is
if paco
alcácer loses the ball
Rubén de la Red was speaking directly outside if he
was saying that it is a card that
could be important for the
remainder of the match, not above all
what it has been used for he is a player who is in
the axis he is the player who always has
to come out  at the crossroads he has to balance
the zones and here we see how he does not
reach the center of the field there is still a
long way to go and I do not think that
Leo Messi's trap should not have fallen
for having me without facing the sleeve
for one side of anything for  others are
trying to find and what does he look like he has
fallen into his trap samuel heads in front of
you ball in midfield the trend of the
match little by little barça begins to change
equalizing the contention  gives understanding
ball
region amos looking for the ball to the
right where gareth bale is going to receive it
down with his chest delivery for danny
carvajal receives luka modric
the player who is always decisive in
real madrid's midfield moves
gareth bale de luka modric puts the
ball in  the superior mobiles
so
that he did was offside
return remember to let
real madrid's starting team dance after his
absence here we see the action repeated and
been a little early
[Music]
madrid
has a very clear idea we have already seen
several times  in which you try to win
the back of the defense
press very high it
will be very easy barça
in his symphony gerard piqué delivered
for rakitic sergio Busquets for andrés
iniesta entering from the left day
for jordi alba alba looking for
surrenders for wii suárez the offer is made
uruguayan delivery for payment reach
leo messi controls play sergio
Busquets barça begins to live in the
camp  or from real madrid jordi alba handed over
by andrés iniesta manchegos leaves mind
possession of fc barcelona Busquets luis
suárez each time
luis enrique's team lasted i think barça is
missing neymar from
barça a
lot in presence of real's pitch
if madrid doesn't find leo messi, there
is no way to put
real madrid's defense in difficulty when he comes
and users are not asking for much to
receive and I think that today barça is going to
need more than ever the argentinian tie a
quarter of an hour into the match
santiago bernabéu stadium the serve of keylor
navas
and he was about to steal luís suárez
throw-in for the white team
looking for that race gareth bale it is benzema
the one who fights with a titín he took the
ball from the center of the french
sergio Busquets is the 5 of the  barça handles
the ball
Busquets floor of the ball and that he be
with ivan rakitic
[Applause]
and that they are the right one for sergi roberto
but you made me look for another
hotel  stegen
and barça playing control football yes,
but control football without
permanence does it in the opposite field and look where
he is putting it to real madrid it is
control football but it is their own area on their
own pitch and there
barça feels a little uncomfortable  fight the
ball ball luka modric a marmoset gets
ahead of the stands iniesta plays for
Busquets again samuel before you
drinking the ball barça wanted not to
wear down real madrid in that pressure;
control that isn't
good carvajal took it away
when i did the balls but
halfway inside christian danger
and avoids the dangerous action that would have
left karim benzema alone against ter
stegen
well that's what real madrid wants to achieve
with such pressure  high that he
is stealing and having the opportunity that
in any unmarking of Christian benzema he
generates
if the driving is planted they
crossed and carvajal
[Apla  uses]
with the lights on if it is an
unstoppable team as I told you it is to turn
later to any option you want to
remove the ball and I think that madrid
has to be very aware of leo
messi because that is where all the trouble will come from
barça's attack sergi roberto
centers the short area casemiro the
counter is coming
2 liters for caribbeans very easy very only he
will continue between for christian christian
out of town because just what the
above I think it is rickety when
seeing messi of that leadership he did not give
continuity  not why messi did see
the myths as a result of the cup but at
the last moment I think he
slows down his career and makes him unable to
reach that ball that the mdl to messi
that is and even the repeated image has
arranged
I thought offside the assistant
understood that he had to cut off the
king's advance
many works for entrance Christian moves
[Applause]
m there is a very clear opportunity that the
execution has not been the best
care ca  mara barba
luis suárez's shot
goes wide after the decade of payment
20 seconds 2
goal to goal but the 0 0 continues if it
is clear that in madrid he is a little
more dominating the game but here it is
impossible at minute 18 to predict a
result because  we have seen in these
last 20
seconds madrid has a very good chance
but in a small oversight it is a
perfect pass that for what to do it will be to
leave it in perfect condition you know
what i wanted it to have to finish
first and a great chance for
barça i think we are facing  a
very high level of classic and everything can happen the
game is beautiful it is beautiful you are
seeing part of the two teams we have seen
before two or three players have shown superiority
a real madrid that I
think has control of the match
but not  It can be neglected by
soccer players who have a lot of potential to do one
and are showing that they have
had several occasions to be able to
do it too
or  In a very active party, the two ethnic groups
are not doing
well offensively, neither of
them is trying to speculate again,
they are trying to be amarrategui, but on
the contrary, they were not going to
play an attacking game and that is making
it a very showy game for them.
amateur he hit him very badly there is luís
suárez before they animate he sends a little
he hit him well because
the truth is that it was much better than how
he could execute later
and this time he is challenging casemiro because
he is
only 10
marcelo for christian ronaldo christian
that he goes against gerard piqué in
a full left against christian
that the others have taken
but it was very hard as an open christian
with blood on benz and leo
messi bleeding from the
grato mouth in argentina it
happened just after what we saw is
an extraordinary hand of  ter stegen yes
again with casimiro we are going to see the
repetition at first it seemed that
nothing was happening but here it was not
recorded with the nation with m  Arcelo Marcelo hits
him in the nose with his elbow,
let's see, let's hope he doesn't have anything,
nothing important, that his nose isn't broken,
but I think Marcelo,
I think it's involuntary, there's
no time he's going to hurt him,
panels and
[Applause]
Marcelo Nessi  They arrive very evenly on that
ball and we see how Marcelo doesn't even go
very strong, he goes
to enter with the inside, they
even took a small jump
that in the end that generates you for not having
stability there because when he opens his arms
he hits Lionel Messi  in the mouth but
luckily for messi
I think it was better in the mouth
because it must have been swimming and it
could have broken his nose it seems
that it is in the upper lip and that he has
made a small gap on the
inside  and when I say that it is not
intentional, it is Marcelo, we know
Marcelo is not a controversial player, he is not
a player
who never goes with bad intentions and
that is why I base myself on that type of thing and we have
seen there what he has done c  Like when he
was with the physio, it was when he
raised his arms due to
inertia itself and I don't think it was
to hurt the Argentine
momentarily, Barça with 10 leo messi
preventing
the Welshman from appearing breaks the offside in
the heads-up  but he throws the ball very
gently to the lehmann goalkeeper
because if he surprises us, i was
surprised that he wanted to define
first because he had won the position
and good control nor would he have given a
much clearer definition andrés
german goalkeeper but if it comes out
That intention that the Welshman
had could have surprised you because he
had a lot of space between 3d in and the
goal, attention to the confusion, another goal
from Barça, the ball to fall in Vail,
we continue with the continuous attack in the
game that you see, he puts it
there, we have not seen it, but  it seems to me that it
came from a throw-in to the mistake in
the defense of barcelona
not perhaps we will have an image to clear
up doubts leo messi already on the field at the
moment  with dressings over his mouth, yes,
because if they are an external gap, then
you put something on it to cover the bleeding,
but to do it inside, it has to be
there with something until it separates or
the gap can be made, danny carvajal takes out the ball
so that he assured that
The Brazilian often turns to perfection, dribbling at the same
time and Casemiro looking for the ball to the
left towards Marcelo
and Roberto Marcelo, go for Cristiano
Cristiano on the left
from Cristiano deviated but there are already many
shots on goal especially from Real
Madrid yes but I think  that there is a lack of
communication between nogales del beni from
behind without a race and he was surely
much better positioned than
christian ronaldo we do not see it
there the psuv would have taken him is I was
convinced and see if it surely generated
more more danger than what
christian ronaldo has done  and this is the occasion
that we talked about before here I thought that
a control that gave him to define but
but be careful that the intention of d  the
welshman is nothing without her finding the
inside comes a vaseline we see that
the german goalkeeper was a little far away
there and it would have been a real
goal for andrés iniesta delivery for leo
messi be with sergio Busquets opening
the left
of Sergio Busquets indeed extra
Cristiano  ronaldo jordi alba
the cancer race let's see why there is no
offside paco alcácer remember and
carvajal but he is very fast on the side
for ccoo he has to be much more dagger
on that flank and he beats those five or
six meters with
oriented control  with his right foot
and getting into the area, they have to
hesitate to work when entering him
because he is inside the area, I think
he waits too long and then wants to do
a dribble, which in one-on-one
working is not easy, I think  that he
had the opportunity to beat the cancer
to have been a little more
like I mentioned before, a dagger towards the
goal of keylor navas or maybe that is why
luis enrique has decided  do put paco
alcácer anticipating this type of
situation instead of a denis
suárez instead of an andrés gómez who are more
midfielders than paco and there
because the responsibility that paco
alcácer has when facing
when doing  one on one we see that there are
situations in which he only has
the support of luis suárez there he has to
make the determination of power in
order to be able to generate the dangerous situation
of five minutes in the hands of luca modric
well of hernández fernández who had
supported himself  the croatian in the arm so
the ball returns to the power of fc
barcelona for this action
seen the repetition is what
hernández has understood hernández
was deserving of a foul here we go the
great save by ter stegen because the shot
is very violent by christian he sees it  he does
everything very fast
when he had us accustomed to these
things at his best the fast moment
although the right and shot to kill
madrid
wants to cut
sergio Busquets
recup  it was the cycle of barça delivery
sergi roberto for ivan rakitic
real madrid lost a great opportunity to
attack a two for two
iniesta
ivan rakitic
the croatian keeps the ball
advancing little by little
delivery for sergi roberto sergio
Busquets leo messi again against
casemiro uno  of the duels of the match
there it is fine if
leo messi dribbles him again the argentinian leaves for the
moment beating
casemiro in that pairing I lie if he does
well to look here severely because he has
that yellow card that now in
any inning only  he's going to think a lot
more because leo messi, even though it seems
that you get to the ball at the last moment,
puts the pointer in your direction and makes you make
contact with him, attention I'm roberto they
take off wide they take
paco alcácer offside but the referee does very well
letting continue
if they lose, in fact they lose, jordi alba takes it
[Music]
roberto contributes barceló leaves the coast of
brega madrid
the referee gets angry the public d  the
bernabéu
the value of modica to the right for
christian ronaldo or in touch of
christian for carvajal
[Applause]
only gerard piqué
to each corner for real madrid let's
keep a bernabéu
totally involved not
[Applause]
in the midfield
of spectacular fiction and  that is noticeable
when you are inter the game mode
both the home team and the
away team is not that breath in public
today is being spectacular attention to
real madrid's aerial power- the
corner kicks will put
toni kroos from the right
pay attention to ramos xabi and the christian
clears ter stegen because of the fist of the
source to marcelo marcelo can put the
center he does it trying to solve
sabino
[Applause]
but after the corner kick the
second ball arrives for sergio ramos
and casemiro just has to  push
to make the first in a ball for
unevenness to madrid
to euro
fc barcelona but well here you can see another
goal this season there
are several who  and they put in we see
how it arrives there there is no
offside there is no offside of neither
Cristiano Ronaldo nor Sergio Ramos
how it arrives at that far post those
plays are very difficult to defend
when the ball is rejected the
defense is coming out it enters from  back
cristiano ronaldo sergio ramos a
little more rushed in line but he finishes off
totally we only see how the defense
of the game forgives he stares at the
ball looking at the ball and casemiro
totally just the only thing he has to
do is push the ball into the net
first goal since  madrid you could see the madridista coming, he was
pulling a lot he was
pressing and it was a matter of minutes that
if he continued without the things the goal was going to
come I have seen a drop in that pique cut let's
see what the team said
calm down calm down and don't agree he
has  What to say that the
calm team that increases intensity that Barça
increases rhythm when the rhythm of the
ball and intensity increases is when you can
put real mad difficulty  rid and if it's
okay in this let's say in this rhythm of the
ball touching the field that doesn't
hurt real madrid in the apple tree they have the
opportunity today to win this classic I think
that barça has football and
dynamics to do more in this in this
match but  don't calm her down with the
calm that she asks for
the leader to bite ahead of real madrid who
would be giving a practically definitive blow to the league
with a six
point advantage over barça who has
no choice but to seek immediate reaction
ball for samuel ortí
the french clone puts up with you he gives himself to
andrés iniesta again a titin he has
paco alcácer but he can't give him the
balls
retracted barça play and play without delving
for the moment
gerard piqué to the right for sergi
roberto when your cousin is just in the
middle  now he comes to ask leo
messi if he is very far from the goal and it is
also if next to cristian or
precisely sergi roberto
the right back of barça comes from inside
whom we have seen very little in the
game
[Applause]
/ good ball for rakitic rakitic
on leo messi leo messi for luis
suárez but for
the brazilian against leo messi's mark he
wants to make the play recovers
Busquets with the ball he sends for sergi
roberto receives  leo messi
menzi goes inside he wants to do the
diagonal month and delivers for andrés
iniesta iniesta with danny carvajal
iniesta who wants to leave the
side of the king
jordi alba falls down the carvajal path
jordi alba now stays with a lot of
space the days we will see
what makes me leave yes for ivan
rakitic Busquets again leo messi
luka modric's mark second a lot realmadrid
casemiro missing on leo messi
he comes back
I think it's barça's fault he is
looking more than ever for leo messi to
be a  little thick when
looking for attacking moves and
even paco alcácer himself from barça who always
plays with open forwards in
wings to open spaces and what  And the
men receive it more calmly,
we see that it goes inwards
as we see it again in this move and
if we jordi alba who is made up of
attack they do not have
for that fact that we have seen it seems
tremendous to me is when on madrid
the  barcelona only three fouls in 32
minutes of the entire game and barça
that has not made any in 31 minutes
is not usual it is not an indication
of everything we have seen in these
30 minutes
also it has been the one that has had the
initiative that has  had the position of
courage is that he has had the chances and
a fire
above
[Applause]
the savior of barça where I read messi the
action of the argentinian does not and do others
leak from the defense the dribble the shot
down to the rescue or if barça equalizes
and one
[Applause] well,
the best player in
history appears I think Leo Messi is today the one
who can make this uneven in
favor of FC Barcelona everyone can
play well but in the end this move is
worthy of him  he goes very well from madrid he
makes a one on one there to
carvajal very quickly and when we see that
the ball is left to his left leg it is
possible that keylor navas could
do something he had a lot of time to
think about a situation that he has
found  a million times and that he
does it like nobody else messi levels the game
and he is the one who can do this he takes
a blaugrana color
a great goal with the cons watching
leonel messi as a dribble how he gets
in turns at the last moment and does it  very
simple from face to face than lorna more
[Applause]
the match that has
three minutes that duel that
we were talking about casemiro is chasing is
symbolizing the match and in the end the
two have been the scorers at the moment
in this real madrid-barça very quick
reaction of the team  from luis enrique to the
goal scored by casemiro yes madrid
has an advantage that casemiro has scored
but as we see the
game christians can contribute things
because they are very well placed
móvi  l and from behind it surprises but on the
part of barça we see everyone
quite thick
difficult care so that he reaches the
ball for iniesta the goal andrés
iniesta
the ball for luis suárez he had made a
mistake in the ball out sergio
ramos
when here we see the goal of  barça and
luis suárez's drag but
above all the control that a month ago and
is dribbling and also as we have said we
must highlight luis suárez who is
well understood in the uruguayan
knew that by letting the ball pass
leo would arrive and he has  left a ball with that
movement without touching the ball
spectacular for leo messi but of course
then the rest has been done by leo messi at
a level that seems easy but I can
say that it is very difficult at that
speed and with the opponents in
front of you he has returned  al barça la
liga
[Applause]
wrong in the pass luis suárez for leo
messi but
balls in the ball out revealed
and also the importance of leo
messi's goal so close to  he goal from real
madrid allows him to continue gaining
confidence in us and fc ar form by losing
the not that has allowed us to be in
the game again and generate well it's in
security
Cristiano
Cristiano who came out on the line d
[Applause
] high up with  this
save by luka modric's missile if apart from his
leg discomfort a spectacular shot
to be the german goalkeeper is also a
very attentive goalkeeper but i already commented
before madrid has many aspects
many options that can create
danger in today's game
problems for gareth bale in the left ankle
because I don't know what will be better or what will be
worse if it could be a twin
being on the ground
remember that today was the day of the return
of mail that he had retired with
discomfort in munich he did not play the
match  back today I went back to gareth bale and
we are going to see if the
problem that the Welshman has right now has consequences
this is the goal of real madrid 1-0
with that ball from sergio ramos to the post
and casemiro's subsequent shot as
the defense of the game that
stares at both sergio ramos' shot
and then casemiro's second move we
don't see it here all the players
play with the triplet they come out without looking without
looking at the real madrid players  It's not
just looking at the ball that's where they
make the mistake. Take advantage, as Rubén has said,
it seems very poorly defended,
but they are the most difficult plays to
defend when there is a rebound and there is a
second option that catches you going out into
the area to get the players out.  players
or leave the opposing team offside
people count down how
they entered Cristiano Ronaldo is chosen
it is the most difficult thing to defend from here
Messi's penalty shot was
very simple and above
all control when  luka modric overcomes
that gives him the life
of
facing carvajal one on one because
I think gareth bale is not going to be able to
continue and the feeling he gave that he
was m  I have seen arches themselves and so coming
to the bench is going to be the
replacement option for real madrid it is going to
decide in society it is clear that I am not
happy about the injury to anyone this is a
strong stick or I will pay after so much
time  stopped but I think that Madrid will
benefit from this
change and another that ascension is the
player much more in shape
is that he has an opportunity to
take advantage of it he
will be a player that Barça will
have to take into account mole  later,
although it no longer has to do with the
game, but the consequences that
gareth bale may have for the remainder of the
season, which is nothing, were minimal
[Applause]
the solutions of the champions
entrance on Cristiano while he is
testing the ascension mark and  the yellow one is
going to arrive
at the beginning the long one let the
game continue but the moments of the assistant
who is the one who communicates to him because there I
see it as the age with him is how he
got up to his assistant is when  or compete
the foul and get the yellow card in
front of you if it is correct because it is a marmoset
Cristiano Ronaldo hits and not the ball
[Applause]
option covers it seeing nothing Cristiano and there is
contact and a clear foul between Bitter
Asensio the change in Real Madrid one
of fashionable men marked ascension
well here we see that perhaps because
coaches sometimes take risks
the risks that a player is not one
hundred percent but still decides to
remove him not simply because of his mere
presence what it can mean
to the team and that is what has happened
with gareth bale de zidane he has decided
even without being one hundred percent because he
had to leave the game bad
luck in the sense that he has
relapsed from the injury there is no chance
to be  for asensio for marco asensio
how good these last few games when he
has started as a starter or when he has come out
in a second half for an
extraordinary performance and level
I personally like it more  the
puck option because he is a much older player, despite his
youth, much more
prepared for a match of this type
but well, you also have to respect
zidane and asensio has not shown that he
has spectacular nerve and bravado
and why is he not going  to be another
day 20 to the ball leo messi ball for
luis suárez in the film it has served
visual does not indicate anything the referee luis
suárez will deliver leo messi messi for
suárez made short he arrives to see if he arrives
to see if he can be
[Applause]
march  If it were
like that, he asks for
a free kick
[Applause]
if everyone from Barça
knows nothing about Leo Messi and they know that he has to
be the one who participates in all the
plays and we even see him with plaster on
his mouth that's incredible it seems but
a  little psychologically you can get
the game by having to bite all that
at all times but but leo messi it is
very difficult to stop it no matter how
difficult you put it,
the players protest because there is
and  Indeed, from his corner a wide
had cleared Leo Messi's shot
and I have the importance in each play in
each second each moment of the game
how this classic sergi roberto is living
41 minutes first part it seems
very short this we are about to
to arrive at the break
a marmoset andrés iniesta the control
oriented to the leaves for sergio Busquets
delays for samuel before you this one with
andrés iniesta the 8th from spain al
manchego handles the ball sends to the
right for sergi roberto arriving at the
dividing line brakes series roberto via  For
Gerard Piqué
and for Sergio Busquets, they seek to
follow
Busquets, who delivers to the right over
again. Sergi Roberto will
withdraw Real Madrid for the time being
while the glass continues to have a
Rakitic concession, if Busquets, Barça
will touch at that point always and at
all times.  trying
to get messi to appear to overcome lines we see that there is
trying not to lose until they have the
chance to give the ball to al
number 10 while there is no other player
to give options in the final meters
the ball ends in the goalkeeper at ter
stegen sends gerard piqué to sergi
roberto la vida iván rakitic goes
there from afar casemiro
before
the pressure on the goalkeeper forces him to
hit the long ball  luis suárez jumps and
sergio ramos takes it to toni kroos
who puts them a great pass for
marcelo the brazilian marcelo joins,
poking the ball but with his chest he
lowers it and they cut samuel on marmoset who
applies it with that quality for 3 iniesta
leads the  manchego andrés iniesta enters
for leo messi messi now leaning
on the right side messi filtered
for the viewer i'm out of the game
life
pressured by marco ascension ends
up on the right of keylor navas work was done in
asencio's defense it was essential
because the center of visuals was
great for jordi alba's arrival
at the far post after
paco alcácer's move to the near post and that
defensive work by asencio has  It was
essential for me to
finish off with total comfort
I went back it would have been a
better option for the shot We have a
second where there were already two
Real Madrid players, each of
Casemiro Sergio Busquets is missing on
Casemiro Final stretch of the first half
We are about to reach the  rest
with the tie for gold first casemiro
then leo messi here we see the
unchecking of payment to which to do back he
would have received totally alone
totally alone and there paco moves very
well those tricks inside the ball area
for toni kross luis enrique was hoarse
he said alone  bus and I think
that even to make this link before
we had the possibility we will go
short instead of hitting long
nacho ball for carlos enrique casemiro
we reach 44 casemiro's change of game
is not a good ball but
neither is the clearance  by ivan rakitic
throw-in for real madrid the
image of cristiano ronaldo from more to
less in the first half started very
put in it for a long time we haven't seen the ball
for modric you challenge it casemiro the
midfielder delivers to the right for
danny carvajal Cristiano comes to receive
but carvajal wanted to put it in
depth recovers barça andrés
iniesta with paco alcácer he makes a mistake in
expansion because real madrid fast
for
asensio barcelona and returns to recover
luis enrique's team
to get jordi alba you have to see the
added time that is probably a
minute for the time he has had to
be attended leo messi sergio ramos
reaches the entire division the captain of
madrid  puts it to the right for marko
asensio control of asensio and the fight
with paco alcácer there is marco asensio
delivery for luka modric modric with the
ball modestly endures and never
modestly with the left that
danger always had on benzema he
takes it out with Busquets quality  andrés iniesta
malla discharge of the visuals danger
attention to leo messi messi wants to remove
messi right  ima prison million
that leo messi
jumps from casemiro over leo messi
to ask for the second from the brazilian if
we see the whole barça team
protesting and it is not that it is a foul
with intensity or in bad faith but
a counterattack is being cut let's say
very dangerous  madrid- we see how he
steps on leo messi's left foot there and
what his fc barcelona teammates are protesting
is not outrageous
because it was a clear opportunity
for fc barcelona and we see that
even messi himself is asking for it for my
second yellow card  for songbook
and expulsions and casemiro is playing
with fire he is playing with fire because
messi is there he is a player who
feels he dribbles he is going to dribble you there he does not
have to enter casemiro there we see how
he steps on him and that is why his career is not
missing from barça iván  rakitic cleared
sergio ramos at the edge of the area
marked asensio passing roberto
to christian ronaldo at the end
211 men were added for jordi alba delivery for
andré  s iniesta iniesta advances meters with the ball
andrés iniesta
returns it to him sergio Busquets again
andrés iniesta 30 seconds to
rest big
nacho because as soon as he touched the
ball he threw himself to the ground something
nacho noticed when the ball
hit him and he  let's see here
right away the image
[Applause] he
makes a knock down supported with his knee
stretched out
we'll see there we see the play as how
piqué says things to
sting casemiro there and a duel in which everything everything
is within everyone's reach to
win a minimum
the tremendous image of psyche
telling noise in casimiro that
rakitic was smiling corner kick to pass a
foul on keylor
[Applause]
later leo messi had finished off alone
and had kicked the argentinian out
and again the idea appears after leo
messi and we see that  there he is
protesting
that the navas the truth is that there is
minimal contact but I think it's missing
because inside the area you can't even
touch the goalkeeper we see that here  he
sticks his arm out a little
is that nothing can be done inside the area
the goalkeeper is missing the first
half ends the barça players
protesting asking for that
yellow card the second for casemiro who has
been very prominent in the positive in
the goal and then also for  those
actions to the limit quick summary
first part rubén a
very vibrant first part very exciting the two
teams have played attack we have seen
many chances by both
teams maybe a little more by
realmadrid and then
casemiro's decisive action that
possibly  it could have been the
second yellow card, penalty,
minute two in favor of real madrid' which
I think is for me a marmoset from above
Cristiano Ronaldo in the area that is not
called but even so I think the
referee is doing a good job and  a
very even game albert
luque summary well it is clear that madrid has
been a little better
two very different ways above all
madrid because the
whole team goes out at the same time and on the part of
barça always looking for the presence of
leo messi who is the one who leads the whole
attack of barça and this second part
because the two coaches have many
things to say to  his teams and above
all, be careful with Casimiro who is not one of them,
he has earned this second
yellow card and he is going to have to be very
careful not to finish, he will end up being sent off
in today's
game luxury commentator luxury match at the bernabéu real
madrid-  casemiro 1 barça leo messi 1
time off in the Clásico at the
santiago bernabéu stadium image of
the real madrid players- remember by the
way that the white team saw
how gareth bale had to leave
injured in the first half he came on in
his place  he scored asensio was the only
change in timing of the match the only
change in the white team and image of
the barça captain andrés iniesta
very competitive first half is the  current real
madrid with a goal from casemiro leo
messi raised and from now on gentlemen of
the network and luque
well let's hope they continue to give us
the show that fractioned us in this
first half
a tremendously exciting game very
good by both teams perhaps
real madrid has been a little
more superior than club barcelona but
chances on the part of both teams
good game
there hasn't been much tangle either tangle
with controversial plays or
ugly situations during the game but on
the contrary i was watching
a pretty good game  well and the match that
is even we will see which of the
two teams is the one that achieves singles
see it well yes according to rubén that
the match is very even
I think that madrid is going to come out with the
rhythm of the game that has come out in  he at the
beginning of the game putting barça
in their own field and he hoped that this
barça would
come out with a much higher pace in this second half than
game and from the beginning make it more
difficult for real madrid to see a
much more active real madrid-barcelona
from the beginning dies with a detail that is
also very important that must be
taken into account this tie is not worth it
for barça if they really want to win the
league  Barça has to go for the
victory, they have to take risks and with
that they can also manage the
match, for example Real Madrid
we are seeing Leo Messi who knows that
in the first half he suffered a
very hard blow
with his elbow that he caused  that
the mouth bled well in the first part but it
seems that this bleeding is more or
less controlled and
the Argentine game does not even need the gauze anymore, which has been
very protagonist in the first part that
has scored the goal for barça and has been the
man  decisive for the azulgrana team and
here is what zidane is saying to
carlos enrique camino for sure that he is
intelligent that he takes whatever seniority
he may have and that he is ready to go  when it
comes to cutting plays when it comes to
entering anyone
one on one that messi and
iniesta face or any player from barça
than leaving him with 10 players to his team
against fc barcelona the
minutes are very long beautiful image of
the santiago bernabéu stadium o  aerial image
that precedes the start of the second
half with the ball for fc barcelona
sergio Busquets first
second half the longer the working day
we are in you when with gerard
piqué luís siever's team that captures the
santiago bernabéu stadium
to the white fans a marmoset receiving
from  Buscats a typical of all the calm
of
finding a pass that at the moment does not
appear before you now when with gerard
piqué the 3 from barça to the right center
of the team make a delivery for zach and
roberto pressured by christian ronaldo
[Applause]
for samuel otitis and  above all barça
leaving it would be very important not to be
surprised because if they got
behind the scoreboard again they
have people  let's say that for the last few
minutes
he's not fit
enough to shoot rafinha due to injury and attacking people are
n't there to be able to
surprise barça's defense
so it would be very important for the
azulgrana group to set a high pace and
be them  those who surprise
leaked ball for ivan rakitic if he loses it
to toni kroos he plays appear or for
christian this control and cross karim
benzema left it shortened microphones sergi
roberto
the value is for gerard piqué
between the lines for sergio ramos
also casemiro leo messi with the ball  he
lied to luis suárez but casemiro was very
good cutting off
the presence that has a great stride
asensio driving access in love
within the rod that advances in the
load center
[Applause]
the central culé if this starts again
like the first part  once again those
internships of carvajal to cancer
stays on top and has to hit if that
sprint leo messi that I think should
be saved for  ra attacking plays
because his team needs him a lot and
we see there that picket rebound that
could have been a great scare
leo feels like defending and
the power of ascension has not arrived in that race
and then also the accompaniment of
carvajal we have seen that  they are
in shape
[Applause]
if toni kroos trains set pieces nor
carvajal carvajal amara with putting the
ball hold on danny carvajal delivers
for carlos enrique casemiro the
brazilian plays on a wide one keeps the
ball the madridista center-back delivers
for carvajal pressuring luis suárez he
raises danny carvajal the ball did not go
inside the real
madrid side- good ball on luca modric
who manages to control the ball he
put it in for marco asensio he returns the
ball for danny carvajal who changes the
game good ball for
[Applause]
there it is  marcelo marcelo on the
front in factory strip
[Applause]
the right to have a few corners
for madrid and they appeared  do again the
goalkeeper in charge
of being hit he loves this was the
area with the inside looking for a post be
careful marcelo the second center to
take off sergio Busquets the ball
went to the throw-in
the second half starts again how the
game started  with madrid attacking if it seems like
a copy of the beginning of the game,
barça was able to react in the first
half but I think that again
it goes through but I was talking solver I
say again that yes that is what I asked for
calm and the team needs to be
much more
with much  more liveliness with much more
intensity because that way the only thing he is going to
do is bail out water and sooner or later
the goal is going to come to him he runs from short to
marcelo very only colic going to come from
marsans two micros ball out
of sergio ramos in the area  chica and
barça conceding a short corner that
almost allowed cross to get into the
area
because i didn't defend the
captain out of the game from cristiano
ronaldo
bad gender  once again
the game of barcelona
the attacking action of real madrid the
fall after ramos with Busquets xavi
has indicated the referee that
offside position of Cristiano Little to
Sergio Busquets
so the massive natural fall is
clearly missing and we are going to  See that Busquets
has nothing in the adductor because
according to the repetition that in a
slightly strange way,
calm hernández hernández to
Karim Benzema for the hard tackle here on
Sergio Busquets in the left leg
the repetition a yellow card
should not have
surprised us either  nobody a perfect marmoset the
record where over marks in 100 the
whole lane is open jordi alba
arrives on the left side the
spanish international delivers for
andrés iniesta he moves jordi alba they
deliver it to him and this song
[Music]
did not go well for him but
he was also  invalidated the move due
to offside of hospitalet
and we will see it in the repetition action
of jordi alba with danny  carvajal
a little ahead very fair but
we are seeing how the two teams
are trying to push their
rival up both in madrid
online especially what is done from
behind here goalkeeper to try to steal in
the rival field
hello toni kroos for sergio ramos receive
marcelo  marcelo threatens where iván
rakitic inside the brazilian marcelo
with the outside the ball with some risk
but it reaches its destination carvajal
luka modric crosses the divide luka
modric the croatian continues with the ball he
stepped on it and delivers it to the sea conscience is
looking for a pass that  meets
christian marco axencia continues and
runs over the ball a bit and loses it
ter stegen depression asensio hits ter
stegen
the ball is going to be lost from
zidane's bench since for real madrid who
wants to surprise this plot looking for
ascension the oriented control of  marco
asensio left it to toni kroos from
german with the ball looking for danny
carvajal who joins let's see  r if
danny carvajal is able to get there he doesn't
get it goal kick for fc
barcelona
a very complicated pass because it's very
complicated especially because work
hadn't arrived there is a tremendous mistake
by ter stegen or game by real madrid
Cristiano for benzema benzema maneuver
wins you go  to love of the world but the
world says that Sergio Busquets can't get in there
lost
[Applause]
interpreting medieval of the mother and
forced
to make mistakes in that exit of the ball
we haven't seen how before 3 peking has
rushed now of sweets that no  he
had no way out due to the pressure of
the three real madrid players
when dawn had indicated here due
to a foul by sergio ramos on
sergio Busquets and it could be that there is a
little contact with the knees but that
is when Sergio Busquets has already given the
pass and even the play was made and for me
he should
n't have called a foul and he didn't
even lose the ball it was due to an error by
sergio Busquets after the pr
sergio ramos otesta for hernández hernández
who read him the primer to try to
control those protests a bit delivers
a marmoset seven minutes into the second
half vain for ter stegen of pressure to
karim benzema ter stegen delivers the
ball to sergi roberto the
ball rises toni  kroos plays with casemiro
barça is having a hard time getting out toni
kross crosses his mind for marcelo enabled position
barceloneta barça
[Applause]
and for me wherever he is good with a
little luck he tried to make it
big for me cani's shot is
great  down to surprise
where the goalkeepers have the hardest time and
opening up and becoming big the
german goalkeeper stops her but a
great opportunity for real madrid and
hopefully for ter stegen ar goes down
he leaves dannika
what has ter stegen done and after  a
start where real madrid is clearly dominating
the goalkeeper salvador fc barcelona-
avoiding
madrid the appearance was very important
of the barcelona football goalkeeper right
now he had once that he was
winning by much more comfortable than what
the game he is having
the ball does not last at all for fc.barcelona we are
seeing there are nine dead shots from
real madrid for only one from fc
barcelona toni kroos give me for benzema
and that
gerard piqué
you want to come out from behind the
personality of piqué Busquets for leo
messi there is in that area where he does a lot of
damage leo messi trains for jordi alba he
prefers to wait jordi alba because he
has no chance of deepening
messi for iniesta  again
leo messi wants
to the right for sergi roberto
he came inside day for
sergio Busquets he leaves her face for
want
and he can't receive the
fight 10 minutes into the second half in
which barça is not found if these
ten  minutes the dominator of the match
is being real madrid as we have
commented before when seeing a copy of the
beginning of the first half and
barça int again  I have been looking in the opposite field for
months yes yes no no they have no
other option
and the truth is that if I were a member of
Barça I would be worried as they
are seeing things
at the end
and the right foot now the savior is that of
killer
if I know a good opportunity  to be able to
play it a new one,
he finds himself with a ball and a control
to make a definition only
and in the end I think that I think that he does
not define well here he does not wait for
rakitic and with the outside he is not
capable of putting it in  one side not here that
lorna you go with him with your foot manages to
disrupt that play but I think it's
more of a mistake by the striker if I think that
here paco alcácer I can do much
more the closest defender of Real left him a spectacular rakitic ball
with 34 meters
madrid makes a
control that is left with a ball and then
more than a shot a definition is removed
from him I think he had
enough time to
contact the ball with the inside of his
leg  right and define so that it would be
impossible for the navas 30 meters to
the goal but there is nothing impossible
for leo messi it was
and the shot did not escape
lionel messi goal kick for
real madrid he knows about the second half
with the answer  from barça to the clear
dominance of real madrid in the form of a
very clear occasion that we see again
for a short time we see here paco
alcácer has time to do more
things i think this occasion is
unbeatable paco alcácer had you here
on occasion to unbalance the classic in
favor  of his team and I see it very difficult for him
to have an opportunity like the one he
has had again because he could have another one
if he found
it the control of the Uruguayan player was long gone
a very fast fame that
barcelona in rome through in the
center of the  field goes very well and a great
pass from messi that luis suárez can
not control well sometimes they
do spectacular things but they have had
the opportunity with a simple control of
stand alone in front of keylor navas
but if the long cylinder has gone and
that has allowed the dolón chest to be very
excited to the classic for loss
of pumpkin luis suárez in the area
dribble to luis suárez but that no one go
cuts about what you look like one wanted
put luis suárez back
[Applause]
for luis enrique's team if
this is leveling off and here the pass is
spectacular from messi as a
colleague of ours would say without control without
control there is no paradise' here
that ball to luis suárez that if he had
controlled  well
with his left leg he would have
allowed him to define a one-on-one with
keylor navas corner kick for
barça 13 second half he is going to hit
from the corner ivan rakitic the
launch of the test
[Applause]
three consecutive times
barça's response
a real  madrid that has started superior
that has started having more chances
but a fc barcelona that the three times
it has arrived has come with a
lot of danger  gro, that is, the opportunity to
have done the 2nd on Saturday kilo nothing or
a control that no that he has
not had he had no opportunity to
materialize the visuals because Rubén has been
said we were talking three
minutes ago that Madrid is the real
dominator of this second part  and in
three minutes, barça has had three
chances, two of them very good that
have not gone
on goal due
to keylor navas's very good intervention in both and barça
is taking
a step forward toni kroos ball
for danny carvajal the side joins
from real madrid
al was looking for christian ronaldo
at the near post ter stegen for the
game has no respite we go from area to
area here the tremendous jump of pique in
the fight with christian ronaldo
if there is between sergio ramos and christian
ronaldo almost nothing the players have
I play several games, they are very powerful, but
because it goes very well to the near post, they mark
the times very well and the shot is very
good. Cristiano waits and complains
because  I think they even
contacted
now that
gerard piqué starts the game day for
andrés iniesta
we completed the 15th minute of the second
half iniesta handles the ball to the
right for sergi roberto
crossing the divide sergi roberto
has on the right iván rakitic we
see some members of  the benches
making lost warm-ups
in the brilliant start from Madrid to
those 15 minutes
that he has set a lot of pace and now a
little bit, well, compensating by taking a breather and
the barça, because he will have taken advantage of his side
meters in the opposite field and now he is
having  plus the position of the ball
for the ball that managed to get a move
so that miro first modern touch could
reach it
but luka modric returns to get hold of the
ball danny carvajal short ball
jordi up passes it to andrés
iniesta the captain of barça
rakitic
is in the circle  central moves
sergi roberto iván rakitic leaves it
for iniesta this with sergio bu  squets on
the left jordi alba gives it to him to
be Buscats but he is very strong and
loses the barça that has more ball as
the label should be a little more than the
real mother and growing in the game with
these last five minutes I have
our  barcelona game with more
presence is not stealing in the rival field
stealing the seriousness of real madrid something
that all day the other way around
[Applause]
lamadrid and receives a very usual foul after
danny carvajal so he understands that
it was a kick that has  given the
uruguayan let's
see if the repetition we see better
luis suárez vida and carvajal
protagonists when the game was
already stopped after the
no he is going to try to put a little of
from the discussion between the two and it
seems that he achieves it
with
this of what
danny carvajal complains and the action of luis
suárez good fortuitous moves
[Music]
well raise the catfish and the existing one
I don't know if it was really offside
but it had arrived in e  ste well to the value
leo messi
in the dividing line at the beginning for a long time
this walk is not going to be good short
let's see what they arrived and carvajal with
many meters
one of the key men in recent
weeks
could move back
such on the cut before
he dedicates himself to throwing  he has a lot of
freedoms but one against one good
opponent's area
it gets complicated there
the barça players have thrown themselves well on top of him partners
of cristiano ronaldo
[Applause]
marshall
the false ones at the bernabéu that we are
witnessing today not the
teams that are demonstrating  his quality
chances arrived he has to be very
attentive
but he is very good
toni kross he with the near post clears
luis suárez ball for luka modric
modric on the right side with toni
kroos 2 against 2 there on the band 2
changing control to marcelo with
him  Marcelo's chest goes out
they chase him Sergio Busquets Marcelo
complicates his life and almost takes it away from him he
killed cancer nacho's ball  for danny
carvajal
right on luca modric bodega asks
christian for modric's pass but he is
very attentive great match today
for ter stegen if the german goalkeeper be
very attentive he knows that today
madrid has very fast people and behind their
backs they can surprise and the extra and
those 45 meters a little further forward
for when there is that type of ball
to be able to be like a defender and get well
to the crossroads or the transfer of Marcelo for very
difficult so that it would
be
better
[Music]
that is used to getting the ball
played to have that  I dominate
the transfer of Marcelo which is
very good
for a td this with Andres Iniesta
attacks Barca Iniesta and Luka Modric changes Iniesta
's rhythm in driving to 3
Iniesta and this is 12 that he does
easily he has done it all his career
after Sergio  ramos- again iniesta
leo messi sends for sergi roberto
delay repeat leo messi
[Applause]
- argentina the second half throw-in
for barça
sergi roberto will take
with  troll to Busquets for Rakitic leaves the
ball action Marmoset now attacking
Barça against you for Iniesta
practically all of Barça is in attack a
Marmoset Sergio Busquets again samuel a
Marmoset
Sergi Roberto Leo Messi
if he wants to put it in for Luis Suárez
then Sergio Ramos in  the front of the
box casemiro under control
avoid fernández's foul for
real
madrid 20 minutes into the second half at the
santiago bernabéu stadium at the moment a
draw on the scoreboard maximum emotion the
two teams looking for victory
marcelo marcelo leaves sergi
roberto  the brazilian does it perfectly they
handed over to toni kroos cross who is looking for
the change of play to the right what a
ball he has put to marco
ascensión
ascensión the mallorquin is going to put the
center second for christian
ah portuguese the ball went down the
back it was difficult  the auction is very
difficult very well real madrid is the
only one that is doing we
have very good presentations left here looking
for  scenso and then as there were 12 unemployed
in the auction area not very equal
real madrid arrives with two players and
barcelona defends with two players there
at any time that they were
real madrid anticipates
barça jordi alba's turn on the
side of the  center area hits is
nacho you control luka modric modric with
paco alcácer's mark luka
modric gets into the wolf's mouth nods
auditory
you can sing
asencio he's going to get tired of the attention he
puts it for christian who finishes off
marc the session only  he left with that
great stride he was generous he handed it over
to cristiano ronaldo the portuguese lives
everything in favor of
the ball over the ball very generous
because ascension in his career he came
with a lot of superiority over Busquets
defined now in one on one with
having this good  but of course they exist, he
was there to push on the other side of the
country and if he stays a little behind and
forces kristen now he will have to
jump and the scorer l  uis suárez now
[Applause]
here there isn't a second of 3
30 seconds
what a round-trip game of the area
area of ​​the bernabéu I know who you can't
pay to comment on a move that there is
another I think the pass from  iniesta is
sublime with his outside of his
right leg and then suárez finishes off well at the
near post but keylor navas has a
sensational racket and cannot finish off it
must be said we have talked about the great
game of ter stegen but keylor that rakitic
has had decisive interventions
in the  opposite side
[Applause]
carvajal the one with goat cross but works
luís suárez gerard piqué leo messi ball
for sergio Busquets leo messi
come feel casemiro change his pace
month and month and he can look for the shot month after month and
the realmadrid goalkeeper rejected it
ball for toni kroos  the
game changer tonic christian
christian against oriented and
christian throw-in for barça
but distributed in the bernabéu
match could be 44 for me one of
the best  It's classics that we've seen for a
long time no chances for both
teams it's a vibrant game
exciting at the end football is that it's
passion it's emotion that's what we're
living in it in this classic it's
spectacular we don't care what team
you are even  that fc barcelona is from madrid
I think he is
enjoying this game it is being
a show a great show
by barça it is the game that barça is
interested in they have to win yes or
yes and they are interested in an open game with
many chances  and let's see if if he wins
the game for madrid it's not
essential to look for the opposite goal,
maybe he would have to try a
little more to have the game under control
because a draw for them is good
but madrid always looks for the
opposite goal the book of  the changes
attention I know if these changes are the
first surprising or not tiring they saw
outside they enter like chis web well I think
that because of the yellow card it is sie  In
a very intense back-and-forth match
in any foul you can keep
one less player, not because
otherwise they don't see that
yellow card, they would surely be on the field for
youngsters because of paco alcácer and luis enrique
has the options that many
injuries have  he already decided to remove the cancer and
rodrigo actions
my right to the battle kick
if it could be my suárez andrés gómez he
preferred between gómez because the defender
is a player who works a little more
so he prefers when they don't have
possession of the ball for being a little bit
more compact and help on that
left flank jordi alba that
carvajal's internships are being very good
I can tell the players quickly and it
will be quick for us because here there is no
truce barça's defense clears ivan
rakitic for sergio Busquets 25 minutes
second half
Busquets  for the event where Messi
[Applause] we
closed bands to repeat
Sergio Busquets at the control to
arrive very well  n
and he presses ascension and makes it perfect
training for jordi alba
81,000 spectators today watching
the football party at the bernabéu
iniesta jordi alba wins andrés gómez
refines another convention the area
started by danny carvajal andrés gómez
the unit transports nacho adds this
for luka modric
modric  starting the game the croatian and
this luka modric sergio Busquets leaves
but leo messi
cleanly takes the ball from him very quickly
kovacic mate self-motivated and ball for attention
to the charge madrid ascension is
right profile another era of ascension my
character
[Applause]
another
what you've got now from what
ter stegen is doing today is
spectacular he's proving that he
's one of the best goalkeepers out there
today,
not just the league
the world I don't know what great game
the soccer goalkeeper franz salvando is doing
to his team this stop is
stratospheric not the short stick where
you do not expect it
extraordinary from this yes he comments  I laugh
because he says these words clouds when
a player with his left leg
breaks inside 90 of the times he likes
a definition to the far post with thread
or young girls or cutters for rack and
land that is short to throw
any racket
here
huge
from the front
in
In fact, if it were
Rakitic's santiago de rave howitzer rifle, place in the
league, change of leader right now
[Applause]
everyone, well, what we're talking about gives us time to
comment on the match, it's being a
real show, we're talking about the
ascension song and here  rakitic
takes a cut from toni kroos great and
crazy in his less good leg he takes a
spectacular shot for unstoppable so
that the navas surprised this 12 because of how he
was but it was the game that
barça wanted and now the job is for
real madrid  and barça is going to be
intelligent, they are going to open up the field, they are going to
have to try to have possession of the
ball and making it endless
is very difficult for  ra to get the
position of the ball to real madrid who
also throws it d
and there is no they cannot get there but navas
you put it very well on the opposite side it
enters at a very good height and good a
game in which real madrid
had chances to get
Ahead of Portugal de Lona has also
had some very clear chances to see
that position ahead of the two goalkeepers
who have done a great job today and
are having a great game,
but hey, Barcelona has
been successful in paying attention to Cristiano,
it is his turn to respond to  realmadrid corner
what a crazy game what a show
we are experiencing in the santiago
bernabéu and now more than ever barça is
going to try to sleep the game a bit
with this 12 andrew gómez's field
is going to come in handy for barça with iniesta
with with  andrew gómez with rakitic with Busquets
and he has a good
midfield to sustain this result
to the corner toni kroos clears gerard
piqué powerful in the center of the ar  ea
luka modric can look for the shot he
prefers to change the pace and center
back clears gerard piqué who
becomes great in the area
kick demand for real madrid 29
minutes 2a
with this result barça would tie
points but because of the particular goal average
they could be the leader  of the championship, yes,
with one less game to play 0 very
offside Cristiano very focused
Cristiano's style
for you
for sure because of zero German and I'm
surprised there that ball look there are many
players but well there are three
players clearly offside and  ximo
wanted the money where is he where is he
looking the boys are looking at the
stands because there they are in the form of fire
two meters no it is not that there is a doubt they are
two meters and three real
madrid players which one or messi leo messi wants to
leave marcelo surrender  for toni kross the
mind to die what a wonder i have
done it luka modric
asensio driving huge cut by
sergio Busquets here is the 5 of
barça enter  ega search hitting the ball for
ivan rakitic he is playing with leo messi
short marcelo there is barceló delivery
for toni kroos the drop shot for mateo
kovacic
comes to receive luka modric let's not forget
that real madrid has already made two
changes and i think the third change
if this continues like this it will be and he will remove
a midfield player and he will have
to risk a little more or even
karim but I think the team
needs and between the lines a player like a
puck who after that is to free the
game to put him in  a 2 to 2 and I think
it won't take long for the city to
incorporate it into the field of play, well,
maybe it will also be purple, also the offensive power
in the midfield,
both Madrid and the nation's chronicle,
we'll see if he said to do it, he has
those options, he has here, month and  be
careful because lucas vázquez is not even on the
squad list off the bench
and the
ball guard for sergio ramos- 31 minutes you
can talk about delivery ramos
for barceló
garcía  rgio ramos hands him
on the right for hook nacho
long ball mega the ball and luís suárez
suárez who wanted to roll goes to
the sideline serve for real madrid the
glass retracts a little sergio ramos
yes barça did their job and  there are 15
minutes left and it is clear that I am not
going to make a counterattack they are going to try to find
luis suárez m yes but as long as they
keep their goal well karim benzema benzema is
on his face they got fed up benzema the
short cop gerard piqué the ball is going to
chase it toni kross but he goes  to get there
leo messi messi went to the entrance
of sergio ramos it's going to cost you 1
clear
red cardboard to do how weird
[Applause]
we are that it was going to be yellow but
repetition we'll see what they make
eternal of the fact to think that the
entrance is to steal if we go to the
repetition to give a little better opinion
for me yes that play that cuts the
counterattack and is a foul and for my
yellow card but let's see
if with that he wants  to say that his
protests I
don't believe him that it
is not true that Donostia attacked from the
front but it is not his turn I think it is
a very clear yellow card
from Sergio Ramos because he cuts against the
attack but he cannot break up the
game like that inside we are watching  a
great game
a team with one less player is a
very big responsibility no I don't think
that they take the referee there
yes I think we have seen the repetition
the truth is that the entrance is very strong and
here we select the plant piquer
all their
protests
[Music  ]
they are asking him now in his favor and
now he tells him well why he doesn't speak
now I think if we bury him with all
his reason because for me I'll say it again it's a
foul and for me it's a card but
it's not red well two friends like
sergio ramos and gerard piqué recognized
or at least that is what they saw he
says they are
facing each other right now
today we are going to see in these minutes hour 12
to the end the real one well
how is he capable of structuring  and
in these minutes you can now read the one about
mateo kovacic bringing
the true santiago story on fire
[Applause]
good yellow card
well a very nice game we were
watching an exciting game he
is ahead of trying to tie a very
important game and there the referee  from the
hub to real madrid with 1 - when it
shouldn't be if it's a red for the game and
a direct red card
how many games with the decisions
that real madrid have from maranello
[Applause]
and we're going to see how to fix that
defensive line now in these last  minutes
like that, they are going to have to
multiply in defense, get involved a
little with nacho and in attack to try to
help the midfield, barça is going to
try to put the game to sleep and make it
attract
[Applause]
impossible
from keylor navas ways I have  forgiven, I
think it was a save by keylor
navas as the girl came out with space
and avoided in the
third match of the cri cri Democrat party
christian
stiano goal kick asked for the
christian and the one who is going to put the city
you did not eat bruise
good player also before I wanted to
say the occasion is piketty who could
have sentenced the game and there was a
clear lack of the chet and in this
case the  yellow card to deal with right
now the game is at a point
where this is boiling
if madrid has to risk
for my very clear foul by jacobacci che
but well done for his team it is
also a very clear yellow card
because for a counterattack but
if it does come  to go to cobach and they
considered a three against one and it was
barça's third goal for sure
and here the
referee made a mistake again because it was a corner in favor of
real madrid who did not concede a
shot from Cristiano but
gerard piqué's leg
[  Applause]
when jaime rodríguez has already entered
karim benzema has left the field of
play
iniesta leaves javier iniesta with
the ball enters cesc  iniesta for luis
suárez hits iniesta himself kovacic
recovers let's see real madrid which
is a team with 10 even the heroic
is not the first time he has bounced games
gerard piqué heads but devaluation
that he looks for is very smart or sergio
Busquets letting pass  the ball
[Applause]
beautiful that was produced by luka modric
if that's why nothing is going to put the game to sleep
without any hurry in that he is a
real teacher he knew that madrid was
going to put pressure on him and that he was going to put that
burden on him and that's why  he lets the ball pass so
that the two collide and a foul caused very well
by Busquets leo
messi leaves he does what he wants
[Applause]
the value that can be lost by the
blanket is going to be protected by ivan rakitic touches
marcelo
where the argentinian does not  It's normal, I think
it's impossible to stop any
player, he makes it clear, whatever
name he has, but it's not there, it's
Toni Kroos, he's a world champion player,
meat from Europe, but when he turns he's
unstoppable and p  for me it is not impossible
with one on one for the missive
kovacic kovacic against his own
goal and I will end up winning
a spectacular two-meter sprint
and he always waits as
long as possible for the time possible to make his snatch
so he does not allow the
rival to maneuver  no and that is where he
is much superior he
is like that player who attracts not that he
waits for the moment when he is disgusted by races to
rip me off he knows that in 23 meters he is
superior to any player and he
waits until the last moment to
decide very quickly he changes  the
address and there the rival is
dead no no he can't do anything
because here we go tremendously superior
foul in favor of barça ivan rakitic is going to put it
ivan rakitic takes out the ball at the
far post fill the pickaxe he touches
a marmoset with his head and the fight can break out
the real madrid counter presses the
concession bar for christians they leave
the white team and christian integrates
for marcelo
looking on the counter side  rio
cafetero before andrew gómez
james leaves it for the incorporation of
danny carvajal he is at the front of the
area carvajal hands over to haven james
who can put together the potential shot
block der spiegel
because it was very far but he has an
exquisite left leg and
I even think they touch some  barça game
that could be seen we see there they play a marmoset and it
could have surprised ter stegen
but luckily it went to the hands he
stole fc.barcelona sergi roberto delay to
the goal
39 minutes in the santiago bernabéu stadium
and right now with this  12 turns
red hot real madrid wants to
avoid it in the remaining minutes jordi
alba hands over to andrew gómez the
added error luka modric steals from me let's see
who knows what the referee is
for real madrid
to get danny out  carvajal
delivers for javier rodríguez receives
toni kroos but turns to mateo
kovacic
the croatian starting the game
casemiro's substitute who now
has to be c  asemiro and ramos in one
and the one from madrid has to be very
specific in the passes because we see that
behind kovacic dryness
with nacho and above me and
luis suárez stay and they will find how to
get the value in hand to hand like
marcelo  marcelo
[Applause]
to the Colombian
I see that it had an effect
for the
near post of gaulle to say for the championship
if kevin enters this, it changes for the
hand the same a draw and a defeat to
cut the points and how jaimes enters
from  back looking for space looking for
the near post here we see how the
entire area is crossed the entire area is crossed
to receive that value at the near post it
is the only one that ter stegen has not been able to
do anything it was a very close shot very
accurate from hammer  that puts the tie
on the scoreboard there let's see how
his right hand tries to get them out
but you can't ask the goalkeeper for more and
I've said it before his speed has
nothing to envy luis enrique luis
enrique no  he has nothing to send to
zidane only in one thing on the bench
that has zidane he has a
spectacular bench with asensio with isco with him
now with jaime rodríguez and that those
options nowadays barça for
different reasons the game does not have them
two by two
and they are going to try to sleep the match for
them this result is good and barça
has to look very carefully be
careful what the charge is going to madrid
if the driving
bases and now he faces power throwing
sea consensus he wants to let
christian shuffle  christian for javier
rodríguez available wait for my complaint
[Applause]
for the victory
and
lack of leo over the german player
in these minutes we will surely see some
chance of the game that
barcelona will see some chance of
real madrid to take the match the
offside of  you know when you go with
this inertia you can't stop the rhythm it's
that with so few minutes left you carry
an energy back and forth in which
you  he two teams want to seek
victory it is very difficult to have to stop
it is not true that the draw
benefits real madrid but I think it will be
very difficult for this energy of the
match if rubén is absolutely right
we are talking about barça and  real madrid
two teams regardless of the points they
have even if they are in madrid with one
less player they always look for the
opposite goal I think today we are seeing a
real spectacle of two teams with
an incredible level I think
that we will have seen 20 chances
for both of us in the match  teams and the truth is that the people
who are in the stadium the people who
are listening to us everyone who has
been able to see this game is
enjoying a show
I can say unparalleled unique
unique spectacle santiago
bernabéu stadium 43 minutes second half and this
has not been  finished the emotions continue
receives the ecover andrew gómez they take
away my balls I will do kovacic with
extra strength this delivery for christian
cr  istiano ronaldo goes for a
christian marmoset in the area and christian
caracolea is holding it he leaves it for jaimes
jaimes puts it looking for bar
el valor takes over ter
stegen barça andrés iniesta
and he drives the ball andrés iniesta
for luis suárez captain
[Music  ]
smooth for sergi roberto andrés iniesta
we seek to be a place that contributes toni
kroos for the players they are dead
the level is has been of incredible intensity
and now on top of that in these
last few minutes back and forth because on the
part of madrid Ciencia and jaime only
he can defend he's going to go to the bottom
[Applause]
with
Cristiano above
Portuguese he goes outside
what a panicked effort of the players of
the protagonists it's
true that the player who has the most
freshness to it on the field is he is
asensio he doesn't know to be true that  he has just
entered he is much fresher but he does not
have the speed to win the back of
fire and barcelona not here yes asensio is
capable with his power and above all that
he is a little fresher than the
defense because barcelona must be able to
face and be able to generate the chance
that allows real madrid that game
sergio
Busquets barça needs to win the game if not
the league will make it very difficult
for Busquets very strong ball and  the transfer of
marcelo
keylor navas
but indeed you are beginning to perceive
symptoms of great fatigue in some
footballers
there is even leo messi himself- take
a little breath let's see the
added time blow to keylor christian
ronaldo heads the ball for ter stegen
plays  gerard piqué let's see how much time
hernández fernando adds because only two
minutes more than time is going to be played
sergi roberto steal point mateo
kovacic stick for gerard piqué
for andrés iniesta
iniesta entered from the left
before and distant luka modric iniesta
for  jordi alba alba centered towards luis
suárez short
let's see if he has a way out to real
madrid jaime cuts himself and shut up I'll have
gomes f  high in favor of real
madrid time is wasting at the bernabéu at the
moment tables that would leave the league
with three points more than madrid with one
game less and with it they will return by the
way even between the two teams
this is the goal that can be worth a
javier rodríguez league
center of marcelo with the colombian playing short a very
important goal very
important above all for continuing to
maintain that income with the game for
barcelona and with so few
remaining games remaining
, james' entry is great as he has entered well in
the  motivated and good game resulting in
this activity the change of entity if
anyone thought that it was not a
successful change because
from waltz half a minute to the end
electric robert series for gerard piqué
I saw that it monopolizes them look for your search
get roberto only when
barça very well  attention o sergi roberto last
time to barça and thickness 5 for 3 with a
lot of people from the bank they give out
sale for between goals andr  és gómez 7
carvajal andrés gómez the goal for jordi
alba
[Applause]
two slight and tremendous end of the game
all the real madrid players go to the ground
you can't believe it
in '92
if you leave the santiago bernabéu
the league explodes  mark leo
messi-cristiano does not believe it real
madrid or barça
allow me allow me in what I speak for
me there is a real madrid error
to follow bértoa and in that action mode he
tries but badly
but he doesn't want marcelo he has to shoot
sergio to site  roberto and not giving him the
opportunity to make that counterattack
jordi alba by bands getting behind
is that leonel as he puts it puts it very
well that nothing can get us a
real crack
in victory to his team rubén what the
hell mistake what the hell mistake we are
talking that we are talking please
look at that player that player
mss and we are talking about a player
please sir enjoy every day you
see him on a pitch you will
never see anything like this again  it's incredible
seeing everything but what about this boy
please gentlemen I'm saying it on
my knees not because he's from barça gentlemen
because what about this gentleman
has no words
thank you for existing and for having chosen
this sport the game has ended in
the stadium  santiago bernabéu a game
that I think will be remembered for a long
time one of the most brutal classics
we have experienced
decided in the last play at the
last second by the man
who probably marked an era
in football leo messi 23 at the bernabéu
barça new leader of the championship
[Music]