Hello.
Welcome to a buzzing Santiago Burnobeau
for what is the biggest
game on the planet.
It's El Classico, it's Real Madrid against
Barcer, and this season even more
important than usual because Barcelo,
quite simply, have to win.
They're three points behind
Ralmdrik going into this game.
A win here for the Blau Granite would put
them level on points with Los Blancos
at the top of the league table.
Rebel Jet Do, of course, have that one
game in hand, but it's a way at Selter.
And they've got a few difficult games
coming up between now
and the end of the season.
So it's a huge opportunity
for Lewis Enrique's side to put real
pressure on Zidane's team
and hopefully force them into a slip up
between now and the end of the campaign.
What an atmosphere here
at the Santiago Burnabel for the
second classico of the season.
These teams tied one all
in the first game at the camp.
Now tonight, it's the rematch
at the Vernobe for Real Madrid.
It's caeleb nauass in gold.
Danny Carverhaul, nacho.
Ramos and Marcelo are at the back.
In front of them, Tony Cross,
Casamiro and Modrics.
And the big news is that Gareth Bale
is back in the starting 11th.
He's been unavailable in recent
weeks through injury.
He's back and lines up alongside
Kareem Pentamar and Cristiano Ronaldo.
For Barcelo coming into this game,
the big news was who would come
in for the suspended Neymar.
Well, in the end, it's Paco Alcata,
who Louis Enrique has chosen
to lead the line alongside Suarez.
And Messi will confirm the barter.
Eleven.
Right now, Terstegan between the sticks is
his debut in a classico
at the Santiago Bernabeau.
Speaking before the game, he said how
excited he was to play here this evening.
Jonny Alba, Utiti Pique
and Sergio Roberto.
In defense.
It's idiesta sekyo Busquet
and Rakatitch in midfield.
And as we mentioned, Pakwalk Kaffir
lines up alongside Suarez and Leo Messi.
Leo Messi, of course,
who scored 21 goals in classicos.
He is the leading scorer
in the history of this fixture.
However, he hasn't scored
against Real Madrid since 2014.
That's six games without a goal.
Messi will be desperate to get back
to scoring ways against
barcer's arch enemies.
He's also on 498 bastard goals, so a brace
here today would see him reach 500.
Well, here's SEC your guy
see a big Real Madrid fan.
Of course,
he's being cheered on by the
entire Santiago Bernabel.
The golfer wearing the famous green jacket
achieved his first major success
in golf winning in Augusta.
A huge victory for him.
And he's invited here to the
Santiago Burnobe ahead of kickoff.
A huge moment for him
and one he completely deserves after
that historic victory
in Augusta in the Masters.
Never before had he won
on golf's biggest stage.
And he managed to do it after a thrilling
contest with England's Justin Rose.
But from one thrilling contest to another
from golf, now back to football.
Back to the Santiago burnout.
It's the two best teams in world
football taking on each other.
And the two best players
in world football as well.
Cristiano ronaldo against messi.
It's Madrid against Parsa,
and it's a massive opportunity
for Louis Enrique's side to put real
pressure on Zidane's team
at the top of the league table.
Three points here for Barcer.
We're putting level
on points with Real Madrid.
And we're on the way now
at the Santiago Bernabel.
Here's Luca Madrick bringing
the ball forwards for Real Madrid.
Modric not playing his
best football of late.
He's certainly not in his best form
since joining Real Madrid.
It's a poor pass from circular.
Ramos out for a bastard
throw on the far side.
Bastard kicking from right to left
in this first half possession.
Back with Real Madrid.
It's picked up by Nacho.
Suzanne will be delighted.
That Nacho's fit
after his other two centrebacks,
both Pepe and Verona unavailable through
injury as the balls
hit long for Cristiano Ronaldo.
Too much on it.
And it's out of play for a Bar to throw
Luis Enrique in his final
ever classico as Barceloach,
of course, the Barcelona manager announced
a few weeks ago now that he'll be
leaving at the end of the season.
Here's.
Circuit Ramos.
Now for Real Madrid.
Nearly a minute and a half played,
and it's Real Madrid who had all
the possessions so far as the balls
played long for Danny Carverhaul.
Turn inside.
Cristiano Ronaldo goes down,
calls for a penalty kick.
A referee unmoved.
It was a challenge by Samuel City.
Well, Christiano Ronaldo was
adamant that it was a penalty kick.
The referee waved his complaints away,
but you can hear that the fans here
at the Santiago Bernabel not too
happy with the official here's.
Casamiro all played into the path
of Marcelo, but there's too much on it.
Look at that incident once more.
Well, Christiano Ronaldo certainly
gets there ahead of Samuel.
And Titty.
There is contact from the big
center back on Ronaldo.
Whether there's enough to send
the Portuguese tumbling to the ground,
I'm not so sure.
I have to say, I think he
went down rather easily.
Here he is again.
Cristiano ronaldo.
And once again it's Samuel M.
Titsy who challenges him this time.
The Frenchman wins the ball and puts it
out for a throw in a throw that's
going to be taken by Danny Carverhal.
Around the corner by Modric,
but it's given away.
And picked up by Pakwaokatha
for his first touch.
The ball finds its way to Suarez,
but he's given possession away.
It was a difficult one for him
to bring under control.
And it's back with Real Madrid now.
And Serfio Ramos crossing into the barcer.
Heart fellow picks it up on the far side.
Back with Serfio Ramos.
Now.
Plays the ball long.
Looking for Danny Carverhow.
Once again.
This time the fallback wins the header
and finds Christiana Ronaldo.
Plays it through back into
Danny Carverhow, who's in space here.
His cross is cleared by Ivan Rakatic.
Rail.
Madrid coming straight back at Barcelona.
It's Madridge on the edge
of the Barcelo area.
Into Danny Carverhau.
Back to Luca Modrich.
The Croatians got time and space
to get his cross into the box.
And it's Ben Zamar who can't keep it in at
the far post and is out for a goal kick.
Time for these bastard players
to have a bit of a breather.
Almost four minutes on the clock,
and they've barely had
a touch of the ball so far.
The Catalan side, so we see that penalty
appeal once more, and every time you look
at it, it looks less and less like
there was enough contact to send
Cristiano Ronaldo falling to the ground.
There certainly was contact, but minimal
for me, not enough for a penalty kick.
Here's Rakatic look like he
was failed there by Casamiro.
The referee once again
allowing play to continue.
And it's bail over
to Marcello on the far side.
He slips and the ball's put out, played
by Sergio Roberto from Madrid throw.
On the far side,
Gareth Bell beaten to the
ball by Sergio Tekiabu.
Sketch your pardon now
with Andrea Finiesta.
The basket players have got
absolutely no time in possession.
It's an intense start to this game.
Real Madrid getting bodies behind the ball
and putting plenty of pressure
on these faster players.
Here's.
Jordy Albanel.
Inside.
Andrea Ciesta.
Once again, he has two
Real Madrid players around him,
but Andrew Sinnesa does brilliantly
well to hold on to possession.
Still within.
Yester, it's a lovely turn from him.
He tries to find Jordy Alba,
but Real Madrid eventually coming away
with the ball
play down the line for Cristiano Ronaldo.
Ronaldo turns inside.
He shoots.
And it's a comfortable save in the ends
for Terse Sagan, although the ball
sit bounced just in front of him.
But he got his body behind the ball.
The German goalkeeper, Renaldo,
did well to turn back inside
one half a yard
and got a good shot in with his left foot,
but a good save from Stegon.
What a start to this game.
Barter finally managing to get
their foot on the ball.
Here.
Serkia busquet in to Samuel City.
Here's Andres Iniesta gets the ball
back from Pakwell Kathar in Easter.
Once more spreads play out to the left.
It's Julie Albal with a bit
of space in front of him.
Julie.
Albert's pass was for
the run of Louis Suarez.
He was offside, though, and it would
be a freekick for Real Madrid.
Here.
Come, Madrid.
Well, Carol failed for a moment.
Thought he got in behind the bars
of defense, but the Welshman was offside.
And it's a free kick for Barcer,
where it's a very tight core.
I'm not sure he was offside.
In fact.
The flag was up early, though.
Gibraltar intern Leo Messi.
Messi picks out the City,
who crosses into the Real Madrid heart.
Surging forward with the ball.
The Jordy Alba.
He finds Suarez, who goes down under
the challenge of Sergio Serkia Ramos.
Lou suarez stays down, holding his chest.
The ball's out for a barter throat.
It was Casamiro who wrapped his
leg around Suarez to win the ball.
He did make contact with the ball.
Suarez back to his feet
and the ball back with Real Madrid.
It's Marcelo matcho intersection.
Bensomar think to front it.
Throw in towards Cristiano Ronaldo.
Play spread over to the right
hand side by Andresigniesta.
Possession with passers.
Now.
Samuel titi city inside.
Crossing into the Real Madrid half.
He finds Pakwell Kappa.
Ivan Rakatic spreads, plays this Leo side.
It's Jordy Albert back into Leo messi.
Four foot touch from Messi,
but he makes up for him.
Finds sekiro brusquet.
Now I'm gonna sIniesta.
Indiesta thinks about a shot,
strikes it with his left foot.
And it was blocked by Nacho Viesta.
Down the line into Georgia
alba back with Andrea.
The Esther, who has suffered with injuries
this season,
hasn't played as much as he or the bassa
fans would have liked,
but he's back for this one,
which is important.
Real opportunity for Bastard here tonight.
The Santiago bernabeau is Gerald E.
K slips.
Was almost beaten to the ball
by Karen Venter mark,
but he made up for it quickly.
The bastard centreback.
Jordy Alba crosses the ball into Suarez.
Suarez strikes one and it's wide
at the far post,
but that's the first opportunity
we've had so far in this game.
It was a good, clean strike
from Louis Suarez, but Nimmer on target.
Always dragging it wide
of Kaylon Avas's right hand post.
Good move from Barcelona.
Had lots of space.
Here.
Louis Suarez to get his shot away.
So two opportunities so far in this game.
A Christiano.
Ronaldo, left footed.
Strike straight at Terstegen.
And a shot from outside of the area
from Louis Suarez, which whistled
wide of Caleb Navas'righthand post.
Ten minutes on the clock.
Nil.
The score here at the Santiago Bernard
between Real Madrid
and Football Club Barcelona,
but it's been an intense
start to this classico.
Ivan Rakatich does really well here.
Ivan Rakatich to hold on to
possession and find Stegan.
After building from the back,
it's, um, city into Jordy Albert.
Albert back to um City.
Got a shot from Garifel.
And there's a bit of afters
between Garifel and Jordy Albert.
Here's Messi.
Great skill from Leo Messi
to get away from Casamiro.
That should be a yellow card.
It's a really poor challenge
from Casamiro.
To be fair to the realm of midfielder.
He went over to Leo Messi immediately,
helping the Argentine to his feet.
And I'm sure Apologizing
just got completely done here
the Brazilian by Leo Messi,
who went one way, then the other.
And it was pure frustration
from Casamiro as he hated down.
Leo Messi conceding the freekick
and picking up the first
yellow card of the game.
Deservedly so.
Twelve minutes on the clock.
Casamiro already in the referee's book.
That, of course,
one of a number of controversial decisions
to poor back past from Gareth fail.
It was almost snapped up by Jordy Albert,
his pacqualcata.
This cross is a poor one
and it's out for a goal kick.
Well, I was saying that was
one of many controversial decisions
in that Champions League tie between
Real Madrid and Bayern Munich.
Casamiro, according to
many pundits and football fans around
the world, should have picked up a second
yellow card
and actually should potentially have been
sent off before Arturo Vidal
was shown a second yellow card.
Many believing that Casamira was pretty
lucky to stay on the field of plate.
Well, he's already got a yellow card
in this game after play almost 80 minutes,
knowing that he can't be booked again.
Luka Modrich in possession
for Real Madrid on the halfway line.
Plays a long ball over the top,
looking for Gareth Bale,
who wins the header fail offside.
The freekick goes past his way.
Here's testegon
jr p K receiving whistles from the
Santiago Bernard Giordi Alba goes inside.
Lu Suarez who leaves it for Pakwaokata.
Now it's Leo Messi into Tokyo.
Busquetz picked up on this
near side by Amber sIniesta.
From city inside to busquet.
Suarez not the greatest pass,
but it's picked up by Sergio Giroberto.
Busquet
well after now doing what they do best,
holding on to possession,
frustrating the realm of players and the
fans here inside the Santiago Bernabeaus.
The Paul stayed long,
looking for Paco Alcathar, who made
a run in behind the railroad defense.
It was too much on the pass, though,
and it goes all the way
through to Kayla Nabasi.
Finds Tessegen, who skept into PK.
Back to Jarrah.
PK booze and whistles from the fans here
at the Santiago Bernabel, all with
the German goalkeeper Mark Andre.
Terpegan slipped on by Suarez,
but he can't pick out Jordy Albert.
And it's a throw for Real Madrid.
Luis Enrique looking for backtoback
wins here at the Santiago Bernabeu.
Madrid,
his side last season picked up
that incredible four nil with it was
when Rapa Benitez was still in charge.
Almost getting through
to Karen Bentomar Jr.
PK did well at the back
just to scramble away.
And now it's Andres
in the Esther into a city.
Jordy Albert.
Good football.
This from Barcer.
Brought forward by busquet into Leo messi.
Leo Messi with a nice turn
in the center circle.
Still with Leo Messi.
Leo Messi tried to t up Ivan racket.
It's just too much on the pass.
It was a couple of yards in front
of the Croatian and he was
beaten to it by Kayla Navask.
Great run from Leo Messi,
who picked up the ball just inside his own
half and ran all the way
to the edge of the 18 yard box.
Here's Suarez manages to get
the ball out wide to Sergio Roberto.
His cross picked up by Casamiro.
Now it's carrying bentamar.
He finds Christiano And
out on a flags up vote.
Really good defensive work from Jerry PK
and Samuel Titty,
who just stepped up at the perfect moment
to play Cristiano Ronaldo.
Our side as we see a replay
now of that Leo Messi run.
Well, it was a brilliant run
and almost a perfect pass.
Really good defending by Jerry PK.
Very, very intelligent.
You exactly where Cristiano Ronaldo was
stepped forward at the perfect time.
Ford comes modricates
with the ball and he tees up.
Karen Bentamari strikes one early.
It's a comfortable savior
again for Tessagan.
The Frenchman didn't get
a lot behind it in fairness.
Centre and stuff is Paqual Kappa inside
Louis Suarez, who took
the ball first time.
It was a sort of half folly on the edge
of the area,
but he sprayed the ball
worldwide of the target.
It was an excellent first touch
from pakwao Cathar, who certainly is
growing in confidence in recent weeks.
He'll be delighted that it's him
who Louis Enrique has turned
to in the absence of Namar.
There were other options.
Harder to round back from injury
and was a favorite for some.
He stood in for Neymar or another
of the front three in the past.
On this occasion, though, luis Enrique
deciding to go with Paquil Kathar.
He's got four goals in Lago this season
so far for Football Club Barcelona.
Paquile Kathar.
Wouldn't he love to add to that tally
here at the Santiago Bernabeau?
And what is the biggest
game on the planet.
His moderates.
Now for Real Madrid.
Inside to Gareth Bale.
Quite sure what Bale was trying there.
Christiano Ronaldo doesn't
either from his body language.
He's not too impressed with that.
It was an outside of the boot cross from
Bail, but it found up certainly nobody.
Here comes Leo Messi.
Calls for casamiro.
And now it's Marcelo down the line
into Cristiano Ronaldo, who swapped
over to the Real Madrid left flank.
With Garethail now on the right.
Ronaldo shot could say from Terse Eggen
and hook clear by Samuel and Titty.
Chance maybe for Barcelona to break.
Now messi's down.
And from the close up you can see
that there's definitely
a problem here for the Argentine.
He's spitting blood
onto the field of play.
He was certainly caught in the face.
Leo Messi, I'm not sure if it's
a nosebleed or a cut inside his mouth,
but he's definitely been caught here.
Well, you can see there
as an elbow from Marcelo.
I'm sure it wasn't intentional
from the Brazilian,
but he catches Messi
right across the face.
I think it's probably a nosebleed.
It's pretty nasty.
Marcelo, I don't think,
is a sort of player who would
have done that intentionally.
It always looks worse in the slow motion.
In fact, Marcelo
is actually bleeding from the elbow,
so I think he caught
Leo Messi in the mouth.
Marcelo's also receiving medical attention
for a cut on his elbow,
probably from leo Messi's teeth
as he caught him in the mouth.
I'm sure Messi will be able to continue.
He's just receiving treatment
on the sidelines at the moment.
Though Barcer currently with ten
men on the field of play.
Suarez does well to hold up possession,
but in the end he's robbed of the ball.
Was picked up by Tony Cross.
Ball over the top from Cross.
Taken first time by Gareth Bao.
It was a really difficult attempt.
The ball coming over his shoulder.
Tried to take it first time,
made contact with the ball,
but sent it comfortably into the arms
of Marc Andre Terseagan.
Looks like Leo Messi is about
to come back onto the field of play.
Good pressure from Karen Benzamar and
says Stegan's forced to hook
the ball straight into touch.
This Gareth Bale gets across into the box.
It's not a good one.
Again, though,
more frustration for Cristiano Ronaldo,
who eventually applauds Gareth Bale.
But his body language told you he wasn't
particularly happy with the cross.
Busquettes into Andres iniesta
iniesta back into Busquet's.
Really tidy football.
Once again from Football Club Barcelona.
Leo Messi plays it into
space for Jordy Albert.
He's going to be beaten to the bull by
Danny Carverhaul,
who does well to find Casamiro.
Excellent composure
from Danny Carverhow in defense.
Here's Marcelo
being shadowed by Sergio Roberto.
Finds Christiano Renault over
and out on the edge of the area.
Tries a strike from distance.
He's annoyed of himself as he blasts it
over the crossbar and into the stands
behind Leah Missi carrying a tissue around
with him still bleeding from the mouth.
It really did get clattered by Marcelo
and Harried every time they're
in possession of the ball as displayed
over the top for Pakwell Cassa.
This time he gets in behind
the Real Madrid defense,
but Danny Carverhaul is back once more
to win the ball back for Real Madrid.
Here's tony cross now.
Modrich back into cross.
Marcello, the Germany international.
Tony Cross once again,
who leaves it for Marcelo.
It's a Karen Benzamarno
a long way from goal.
The Frenchman as he picks out Modich.
Hamburg by Madrid,
according to the referee.
And it'll be a free kick for Barcelo.
Well, they've won five of the last
ten trips to the Santiago Bernabel.
Probably the most memorable victory
in recent years was
six two in Pep guardiola's.
First year come, Madrid
robbed of the ball by Sekio Busquez,
who's magnificent once again in defense.
Brilliant from the midfielder possession.
Back for Barcer.
Here's Racketitch,
of course, coming
in the 2008 2009 campaign.
The year that after one
the treble under Pep Guardiola.
It was a vital game as well, because
they were only four points ahead of
Real Madrid in the league at that stage.
And a victory for Real Madrid.
We've taken them to within a point
for Football Club Barcelona, but
Madrid were absolutely destroyed.
Despite taking the leads
on that night for Gonzalo Higuain.
They were beaten
six two by guardiola's Barcelot.
The first night, in fact, that Leo Messi
was played in that false nine role.
And what a successive proved to be
as Ramadan who are having more
success at the moment, though.
And it's the whites at the other end.
Garret Fail tried to turn back inside
Jared PK who's just telling his teammates
to calm down a little bit
as the Spain international put
the ball out for a corner kick.
So it's a corner for Real Madrid.
Good challenge that was by Jared PK.
Corner for Madrid here.
Plenty of bodies back for Barcer.
It's punched clear by Tessegen.
Jared PK went up for it as well.
Put back into the mix.
Nice off the post, surely.
Now is Casamiro,
where's the first goal of the game.
And it's scored by Casamiro.
It's his third goal of this Laga campaign.
It was an excellent cross that was
put back into the box by Marcelo.
The shot rebounded off the post and fell
very kindly for Carlos Enrique Casamiro,
who slotted the ball home for the first
goal of the game here
at the Santiago Bernabet.
As the cross is played in christiana
Ronaldo is in an onsite position.
Bigger part, but it's circular.
Ramos, who makes contact with the ball.
It comes back off the post.
It's very kind for Casamiro, who just
has to put the ball into an empty net.
Ivan Rakatic was sliding in,
but there was nothing that he could do.
So Casamiro with his third goal in La Liga
of the campaign
and the first in this classico,
making it with 29 minutes on the clock.
Round.
Widthrid One Football Club Barcelona.
Neil from City.
Jr.
PK Jerop.
He came to Samuel City.
Leo Messi.
There was bit of white tissue in his mouth
after being clattered by Marcelo.
The bleeding still not stopped.
Here comes Jarra PK surging
forward with the ball.
Finds Rakatitch.
Now it's messy.
Messy's past intercepted by Marcelo,
now picked up by Sergio Busquets.
Leo Messi.
He's got Sergio Roberto
ahead of him instead.
Goes inside to Diesta.
Finds Jordy Albert, Danny Cava
hall momentarily on the ground.
It's really good pressure
from Madrid, though.
Just no way through for Football
Club Barcelona at the moment.
Messi surrounded by three
Real Madrid players.
And when he gets a free
kick this time, Leo Messi.
Dan's not happy.
He felt it was just good pressure
where it was clearly caught.
Leo Messi by Casamiro,
who stood right on his foot.
Rickett's taken short here's.
Samuel City.
Every white shirt behind
the ball for Real Madrid.
And the faster side at the moment,
finding it very difficult to cut
through this wall of white shirts.
Here's messi into busquet.
Busquetz finds racketish.
Great football from Pasta.
Here's Leo Messi.
And there's the first goal of the game
for Football Club Barcelona,
who equalize here
at the Santiago Burnabeau
with an absolutely stunning team goal.
What a brilliant move
that was from Barcer.
Just as it looked impossible to cut
through this defensive Real Madrid size.
While they found a way between
Nesta Buskets and Leo Messi, they're just
unstoppable this bastard side sometimes.
It was a wonderful move.
Finished off in real style
by the top scorer in La Liga.
Watch this rakertitch into messi.
Brilliant touch from Messi to get
away from Danny Carverhal.
And a fine finish beyond.
Kayla nervous and into the back
of the net to make it round Madrid.
One bastard, one.
And game on here at the Santiago Burnout.
What a goal that was
from Football Club Barcelona.
Well, there you see Christiano Ronaldo's
reaction to that fine, messy strike.
Nothing he could do other than watch
on his gareth Bale now strikes one, fail.
And it's terrible.
Really gets right underneath it and blast
it over the crossbar
into the stands behind.
Some fans would have preferred
to have seen Escope, or maybe Marco.
A cento in the starting
11th for Real Madrid hit.
It was Bail, though,
who recovered from his injury and got
the nod from Zidaneid Zidane.
Long ball over the top from Terstegon,
looking for the run of Paco Al Kaffir.
Certainly something that bastard tried a
few times in this game, mixing things up.
It's a really poor part
of the back from Serkio Ramos.
Possession gifted back to bastard.
And the ball over the top for Suarez isn't
a good one from Ambassador and Esther,
as we see this move again, it was
Rakatiti who played it inside to Liamzi.
What a fine goal that is.
Excellent football.
From Barcelona.
Tony Cross.
Terrible pass from Tony Cross into Suarez.
It's not a good pass from Suarez either.
He was looking to pick out Messi.
And it was intercepted by Serkio Ramos,
who read that one very well.
Here's.
Marcello tony Cross.
Carverhel Ronaldo.
Now it's Madridge space opening up for
Luca Madridge who strikes won Goldwood.
It's an excellent save from Terstegen, put
back into the mix by Christiana Robbers.
Been swung out of play,
and it'll be a goal kick.
Really good strike this from Luca Modrich,
and an even better say
from Tersenegen diving to his left.
Well, there wasn't enough
pressure on Luca Modrich.
Far too much space for him to get his shot
away,
but it wasn't a bad effort
from the Croatian, but a very,
very good stop for Mark Ambert Estegen.
Well, Gareth Bale at the moment is down
for Real Madrid, and they may
have to make a change here.
Bail, perhaps force back too quickly.
He's holding his calf muscle, I think,
and it's an opportunity for Barcer to
have a bit of a drink and a discussion
with the manager.
Lewis Enrique chatting to
Inniest and Leo Messi.
Well, we're just seeing confirmation there
that Sekiro Ramos
certainly wasn't offside.
He was in line when that ball was played.
Over the top.
Ramos, his shot coming
back against the post.
And Casamiro finishing off,
as we see Leo Messi's goal.
Wonderful turn to get
beyond Danny Carverhal.
It's a good firsttime pass
as well from Ivan Rakatic.
Brilliantly.
Finished off by Leo Messi.
Wonderful team goal from
Football Club Barcelona.
That's how you do it, says Louis Enrique.
Just at the point where
Madrid had gone a goal up.
Got everyone back behind the ball
defending,
and they were looking almost impossible
to break down as Gareth Bale
is going off here.
And he's going straight down the tunnel.
This doesn't look good for the Welshman
Real Madrid.
We're going to be forced
into an early change here's.
Sergio Roberto.
He's up.
Messi not the best first touch
this time from Leah Messi.
And it's Karen Benson.
I bring it forward for Real Madrid.
His pass inside is for cristiano.
Ronaldo he's challenged by Samuel City,
and it could be a yellow
card for the Frenchman.
That's certainly what the Real Madrid
players are suggesting.
It's Marco Ascension.
Who's going to come on for Real Madrid
to replace Gareth Bayle?
And there's a challenge from Samuel M.
Titty when he certainly didn't
get anything on the ball.
It's a late challenge
of Christiana Ronaldo,
and it looks like it'll be a yellow card.
Forum Titty.
And a free kick for Elm Madrid.
So.
Two players in the referees book.
Samuel Titty, Cabasa and Casamiro
real Madrid.
And it's Garapelle who's forced off
to be replaced by Marco as Cincio
back into the goalkeeper
57% possession for Cobalt Club Barcelona.
Dominating these are possession
stats here at the Santiago Bernabel.
Here comes Suarez.
No foul according to the referee.
Now it's Messi back over the top,
looking for Suarez.
Back to Leo Messi.
Leo Messi's shot it's.
Just wide calm.
Navas was scrambling across his goal line.
Leo Messi adamant that it should have been
a corner kick, that the Costa Rican
got something on the ball.
The referee deciding not and handing
round madeRED a gold kick.
Well, no, Kayla Nava's got nowhere near
it, but it did take a deflection
off Danny Carverhal.
I suppose it's easy for us
to see with a couple of replays.
I have to say live,
I didn't notice that the ball
took a touch off Danny Carverhouse
leg on the way through.
Testagon with skill and a good
pass out wide intergioberto.
Who gets a better of Marcelo Sanjuam?
City keeps this one in play and finds
Zandri Siniessta
anista once again
over to the far side,
where it's picked up by Sergio Roberto,
where it's lived up to the spectacle.
This first half, without any doubt,
we've seen some excellent
football from both sides.
That bastard goal, without a doubt
the highlight of the match so far.
But Real Madrid have played their part two
on what's been an enthralling
contest so far.
They're very well organized.
This Madrid side under Zidane pressuring
high up the field, giving
Barcer no space or time.
However, Barce is showing
that they can move the ball
like no one in world football.
And even when a side.
Does get eleven players behind the ball,
they can carve out an opening, which is
exactly what they did for that Leo Messi.
Golf
head of One by Serkio Ramos It's back
with Real Madrid now,
and it's Marcello on the far side.
Marcello's ball into the box.
Not a good one.
It's brought down by Samuel City
and flicked into the path of Andrest.
Andiesta now it's Leo Messi.
Messi down the line.
It's a Suarez.
Bit of space here for Barcer.
Suarez's ball across.
It's a jordy.
Albert.
His short just wide.
Another good move from Barcelona.
Once again,
they cut open this realmdrid side at the
back there's Tony Cross into Nacho now.
Christiano Ronaldo.
There was certainly no offside
in the build up to that chance.
Casamiro for Real Madrid
put out a play by Ivan Rakatic.
It's gonna be a throw in for Round,
which are deep in the bars of half.
Marcelo insert Tony cross.
That's Casamiro on a yellow
card, don't forget.
Picked up a yellow for a cynical challenge
on Leo Messi after just twelve minutes.
Poor from Pakwell Kaffer.
Straight out of plate
and a throw in for Real Madrid.
Equally poor from the white so
in possession, gifted
straight back to Barcelo.
It's a throw in for Jordy Albert.
Good first touch from ASENCIO.
He leaves it for Luca Modrich.
Luca Modric.
Again, excellent challenge from Jory Alba,
who spotted the danger there.
It could be a chance
for Barcer to break it.
It's messi with Ivan Rakatic outside.
And messi cuts back inside
and it's a late challenge by Casamiro.
Messi suggesting that it was a cynical
one and should be a second yellow card.
Gerald P.
Kate saying much the same.
So to his Sergio Roberto.
Casamiro, I think,
is going to be lucky here.
This could easily have
been a second yellow.
Well, there's no question
that he catches Leo Messi.
It's not as cynical as the first one,
that's for sure.
But he stamps straight on Messi's toes.
Well, Luis Enrique of the same opinion
that that should have been a second
yellow cards for Casamiro.
Third foul of the game.
He's on the yellow cards and he's
going to have to be very careful now.
Rakatich plays a ball into the area.
Um, titty underneath it.
Can't win the head alone.
Mr.
Sensio gets something on it.
Turned back into the area
by Sergio Roberto and cleared
by Real Madrid, but picked
up immediately by Barcer.
Jordy albert iniesta.
Andrest iniesta.
Weighing up his options.
Just 30 seconds of additional time to be
played at the end of this first half.
And Barcelo have got a corner.
They're going to have to take it quickly.
We've had 46 and a half minutes,
and there'll be two two minutes
of additional time with jolie Alba was
frustrated with himself that he knew there
was a really good chance for Pastor.
Jr.
PK making his feelings very,
very clear to Casamiro.
A rye smile from the Brazilian.
There'll just be time for this corner
to be taken before halftime.
Yvonne Rakati with it,
since it's sailing towards the back.
Poster.
What a chance.
What?
A chance for Leo messi.
Kayla Navas came out for the ball,
didn't make contact with it.
There was Leo Messi,
but he couldn't find the target.
What an opportunity this was
right on the halftime whistle.
It's almost an open goal.
It does come to Leo Messi very,
very quickly indeed.
And in the end, that was the last
chance of the first half.
An entertaining first half of football
here at the Santiago Burner Ballet.
Finishes Real Madrid.
One barcelone.
Hello.
Welcome back to the Santiago Burnobel,
to the second half of this
enthralling Classic.
Oh.
Between Real Madrid
and football Club Barcelona.
What a first 45 minutes
here at the Bernabeau.
It was Real Madrid who scored first,
casamiro putting the whites
one up in the first half.
But before halftime,
Liam Messi leveled things
with his 22nd goal in this fixture.
22 goals in Classicos.
He's the highest ever goal scorer
in these games between Rail Matrix
and Football Club Barcelona.
And that's now 30 goals
for the season for Leo Messi.
And not only that, it was a stunning goal
as well, putting it into a really
good team move by Real Madrid.
By Barcelona.
Pardon.
It was Real Madrid who probably
started the stronger.
They had a good few minutes
at the beginning of the game,
dominating possession,
creating goal scoring opportunities,
and then found the first
goal through Casamiro.
But after about 15 minutes,
it was Barcelona who completely bossed it
here in Madrid, and they well and truly
deserved the equaliser when it arrived.
Casimiro picked up a yellow card.
A bit of controversy at the end
of the first half when he could have
potentially picked up a second one
and being given a red.
However, the referee decided not to book
him a second time,
although Casamiro will have to be
very wary in this second half.
You get the feeling he won't be
let off again by this referee.
So we're on the way here then,
at the Santiago Bernabel
barcelo in the second half.
Playing from left to right,
Jared PK on the ball, who finds
Sergio Roberto Test two in Tilm City.
Here's ambulance in the Esther
with a first time pass out
wide into Jordy Albert.
Jordy alba surging forwards
crossing into the Real Madrid half.
He's caught late by Luca Modrich,
and he'll be a free kick for Bassett.
Getting a bit of a talking too
from the referee.
The ball through to Suarez,
cut out by Casamiro.
And here come Real Madrid.
It's ASENCIO on the far side.
He was a first time substitute,
of course, for the injured Gareth Bale.
ASENCIO goes out wide to Danny Carverhow.
His past put out for a corner by Jerry PK.
Good defending from jerry PK,
who read that one very well
indeed as the ball came across.
There's always a danger of scoring an own
goal in that kind of situation as well.
But it was well judged by Jerry PK,
who intercepted the cross
and put it out for a corner.
So around corner, then,
it's going to be taken by Tony Cross.
Tony cross's corner
headed clear by Suarez.
Picked up by Leo Messi.
Both Real Madrid attackers into
defensive positions at the moment.
And Leo Messi's robbed
of the ball by Modrich.
And now it's Danny Carverhal.
Here's Katamiro.
Now it's Nacho for Real Madrid.
Good term by Danny Carverhel.
On the far side now it's Luca Modrich.
This part is intercepted,
but possession still with Real Madrid.
It's picked up on this
near side by Marcello.
Marcello taking on Rakatitch,
finding Tony Cruz.
And it's a good effort.
And an excellent save
by Mark Andrew Tegan,
who got a very strong right hand
to the ball and put it out
for a Real Madrid corner.
And it's the German, Tony Cruz,
who goes across to take it.
Excellent save from testagon.
Marcelo's.
Cross into the box.
Headed clear by circuit busquets.
And it rolls out for a Real Madrid throw.
Leo Messi putting an end in the first half
to a recent poor run against Real Madrid.
He's got more goals than
anyone in this fixture.
22 now.
However, he hadn't scored
against the White since 2014.
It was a six game baron Spelt,
but he put an end to that in the first
half with a magnificent solo effort.
Here's Marcelo knocks it back
into Tony Cross, who puts a cross in for
Cristiano Ronaldo.
It was over him, though.
Ronaldo complaining about something,
suggesting it should have
been another corner.
I think,
in fact, it's going to be
a free kick for offside.
Ronaldo in an offside position when
that ball was floated in by Tony Cross
by Karen Benzamart.
It looks a little bit of pain here.
Sekiro Bouquet.
I think he's going to be okay.
He was certainly caught late by Bentomar.
Maybe the Frenchman lucky not
to pick up a yellow card.
It was a very clumsy
challenge by the Real Madrid.
Number nine.
He went right through
the back of Serfio Busquet.
Maybe give him the midfielder
a bit of a dead leg.
Ivan Rakatic picks out omciti.
Good skill from Samuel City.
He sets up Jordy Albert on the far
side for Football Club Barcelona.
Albert cuts inside,
finds Andrest in Easter in Esther back
over the top, looking for Jordy Albert.
He was offside, though.
The referee's whistle went late.
Not sure if the flag went up late.
I'm not sure he is offside.
You know, I think Marcelo may have
been playing him on this near side.
Well, as it stands, it's exactly the same
result that we saw at a camp
now earlier this season.
Nothing between the sides on that occasion
as they played out a one all draw
so far tonight.
It's exactly the same score line.
After Casamiro gave round, we did the lead
in the first half.
Was forced off, injured,
hence the introduction of Marco Arsentia.
Tony Cruz switching play over
to the far side, it's Danny Carver.
Howard made a good run,
but he can't keep that one in place.
It's a goal kick for Testegand.
It was wasted by the German as
Danny Carverhow picked up
possession for Real Madrid.
Can't play by Farcer at the back, though,
and brought forward now by Busquets.
His past doesn't quite pick out Messi,
but he has won a free kick.
Here.
Circo Brusquettes, which Circo Ramos
isn't at all happy with.
Really got right into
the face of the referee.
Remonstrating with the official.
I thought he was going to talk himself
into a yellow, but he's got just
a talking to from the rest.
Brick taken backwards by Jerry PK.
Into Terstegen.
It's with the German
goalkeeper once again now.
Samuel MTTI on the far side.
Marcandre Terse.
It's a good pass into Sergio Roberto
who just stands on the ball
and possessions back with Real Madrid.
It's.
Tony cross slid through for Marcelo.
Marcello's Cross is a good one.
It was Ben Zamari got his shot on target.
Tersetegan made the save.
I'm not sure how much he knew about it.
The German goalkeeper
for his positional play.
Once again, excellent hit.
Mark Andrew Tersetergen.
It's good buildup from Real Madrid.
A nice pass from Cruz into Marcelo.
The header from Bentamar, and well,
it's a brilliant save from Tersenegin.
Pure reflexes from the German as he got
a foot to the ball and managed to put it
out for a corner kick as the shot
comes in from Danny carbohauer.
You can tell it was close because it had
Mark Andrew Teslagen scampering across
his line and diving to his left.
Jerer PK tried to switch play over
to the far side, but Jordy Albert
can't keep that one in play.
And Ram Madrid has started his
second half very well indeed.
No time or space for football.
Club Barcelona in possession
and they're really struggling
to hold onto the ball at the moment.
We've seen barely nothing of Leo Messi
so far in this second half.
Pasta just can't get the ball
to the Argentine, who was so
influential in the first 45 minutes.
Having said that, here he is, Leo Messi,
and it's out wide now to Jordy Albert
ambulatories.
Between the two of them now.
It's Sergio, Roberto Jr.
PK trying to pick out Yvonne Rakatic.
Well, here's that chance again,
and you can just see what a magnificent
save it is from Marc Android.
Tersetegen
got his left foot across in front
of the ball and put it out for a corner.
Good play from Rakatich as
he spits it out to the left.
Gets a ball back,
and now it's Pakwalkatha.
What an opportunity there for Pakwalkatha
as he tried to poke the ball into the back
of the net with the outside of his boot.
Had lots of time there.
The former Valencia striker
Kayla Nervous did very well
in the end to make the save.
It's a freekick now for Real Madrid,
for the realm of fans and players.
Don't feel that was a foul on Leo Messi.
Let's see this one again.
Wow, he's clearly tripped.
No question about it.
Clearly tripped by Marcello.
And here's that chance
again for Paco Al Kaffert.
Well, he had a great opportunity
to strike it with his left foot instead.
Tried to topok it with his right
into the corner, and it was a pretty
easy save in the end for Caleb Navas.
What a chance that was.
Well, it's a free kick now for Bastard.
In a dangerous position, well and truly
in goalscoring range for Leo Messi.
Here.
He's standing over the ball.
So to is Ivan Rakatitch.
Looks like it will be Leo Messi to strike
it, and he does and sends
it over the crossbar.
Well, it wasn't even close
on that occasion from the Argentine
looking for his 31st goal
of the season, 22nd or 23rd?
Begu pardon.
In classicos
and 500 for Football Club Barcelona.
He's teaching on the edge
of that milestone with 499
Bastard goals currently.
Here is Leo Messi.
Plays it through the middle for Suarez.
Well, it's a heavy touch
from Louis Suarez, which takes a ball all
the way into the goalkeeper Caleb Navas.
Another great opportunity for Barcer,
but for a slightly heavy touch
from Louis Suarez.
That could have been another
fantastic goalscoring opportunity.
Nacho being shadowed by Pacqual Catheter
Suarez, who's got the ball here.
Louis Suarez tried to play it back
into Paquil Kathy, who was
on the edge of the area.
And it's out for a passer corner.
Danny Carverhow with a last touch.
Well, here's that chance
we saw just a moment ago.
They are Messi threading it through.
And a heavy touch from Suarez takes
into their grateful arms of Caleb nerves.
The realm of goalkeeper
also have just their second
corner of the game racketish.
Who's going to float it in, looking
for Gerard PK, who wins the header.
It's a magnificent save from Kayla Navas.
Gerard PK thought he'd scored that.
It was a great run from PK.
Superb contact on the ball as well.
What a save that is from Kayla Navas
diving to his left.
He got both hands behind it and managed
to palm the ball away to safety.
Good goalkeeping on this
occasion by Kayla Navas.
CRR.
PK, though, coming very close to putting
pasta in front for the first time tonight.
Tony Cross into Serkio Ramos.
Marcello Danny asensio picked up
by Karen bentomar into Marcelo.
Now, Tony.
Cross again.
He picks out the run of Danny Carverhau
on the edge of the Real Madrid area.
His cross gathered by Terse Tagin.
And it's an opportunity
for us to see once again.
That headed effort from Gerald PK.
Jumped brilliantly,
made a really good connection
with the ball as well,
but couldn't direct into the corner,
which allowed Caleb Navas
to make the safe.
Here is Jr PK on the ball
when he loved to score.
Here again at the Santiago Bernabeau.
Brusquettes into Rocketitch brusquettes
once again right on the halfway line.
He picked out Om titty.
Good skill from Om Titty to get away
from Marco isencio and his past to Suarez
was deflected, which made it difficult
for the Uruguayan to control it.
And it's picked up now by Kayla Nabas.
Casamiro's past is a poor one.
Intercepted momentarily by Paco Alkatha,
but he couldn't keep hold of the ball.
And it is back with passing out here's.
Racketitch in yesterday.
A misplaced pass goes out of play.
There's nothing that Joy Albert
could do to keep that one in.
And it's a throw in for Real Madrid.
A wonderful atmosphere here at the
Santiago Bernabeau, as you'd imagine.
Not only is it el classico,
it's a really important el classic coat
and must win for Football Club Barcelona.
Cover not happy at the moment.
He felt he got clattered
by Louis Suarez here.
Both players getting a talking
to from the referee.
I don't think it was deliberate, was it?
Having seen the replay, suarez played
the ball while he was down on the ground.
Hit catch,
Carverhow, but nothing in it really,
as the balls played forward for ASENCIO.
Excellent goalkeeping once again
by Mark Andrew Testegon,
who came off his line chested.
The ball down magnificently.
Well, cool, calm and collected as always.
The German.
Here comes Danny Carverhel
now for rail mode.
With a bit of space to run into it's.
Got Madridge out wide.
Finds Modrich back to Danny Carverhalt.
It's clumsy from Karvahalt as
the ball gets away from him.
And it allows Bastard to hook it.
Clear now.
It's Marcelo.
Marcello goes on the outside,
gets his cross in.
And it's flicked to safety
by Jordy Albert.
Marcelo trying to get
the crowd behind them.
Excellent cross from Marcelo.
Really good.
Defended by Jordy Albert.
He had to make contact with the ball there
because Christiano Ronaldo made
a very good run in at the back post.
So it's a corner for Madrid.
Totally cross with it.
Once again, it's headed
to safety by Suarez.
At the near post.
There's Marcelo luca Madridge.
His cross gathered by Terstegen ronaldo
has been very quiet in the second half.
We've barely mentioned it.
Neither he nor Leo Messi
have seen too much of the ball
so far in the second half.
Back past from Marcelo.
Not the best.
Okaylon, now that's just
decides to poof it into touch.
If you pass the substitutes
warming up on the touch line.
Javier Mascarano amongst them.
He's just returning from injury.
Javi Masarano on the bench here.
Maybe Lewis Enrique not feeling
he was quite 100% iniesta.
Lovely footwork from Andrest
iniesta racketitches.
Ball in.
It's cleared by Serkio Ramos.
Now it's Leo Messi toe poked out
wide into Sergio Roberto Messi.
Once again.
He runs into Casamiro,
and it's a throw in for Parsa.
It says y Roberto.
Now.
It's Leo Messi.
It's pulled over the top.
Looking for Suarez,
and it's a foul by Pakwalk on Casamira
and a freekick for Real Madrid.
Play switched to the far
side by Real Madrid.
And it's picked up by ASENCIO.
His cross towards Christiano Ronaldo
tried the spectacular.
Couldn't send the overhead kick gowards,
though you see in the replay,
the ball actually came off.
Ronaldo's Knee is Jordy Alba,
just outside the Real Madrid area.
His cross deflected, or blocked,
I should say, by Nacho.
Spends a mark for Real Madrid.
It's a good ball from him.
Into Asncio.
He's got Cristiano Ronaldo in support.
Finds Ronaldo.
Oh, what a miss.
What a miss from Cristiano Ronaldo.
What an opportunity for Real Madrid.
And Ronaldo really should
have scored, and he knows it.
The goal was at his mercy.
Hit it's.
Excellent play by Karen Bentamar,
who sets up ASENCIO his fall across
for Cristiano Ronaldo was just asking
to be tapped into an empty net.
Ronaldo got it all wrong.
He was leading right back
and lifted it over the crossbar.
In fairness to the Portuguese,
the pass from ASENCIO was a little bit
behind him, but it had to go backwards
to keep the Portuguese on side.
At the other end,
there's a chance to Suarez.
Oh, what a save.
Well, this second half potting up now.
Chances at both ends.
The latest falling for Louis Suarez, whose
effort was very well saved by Kala Navas.
What a pass this is from Andres
in the Esther,
where the outside of the boot into space
bounces up just in front of Suarez,
who catches it on the half volley.
Very cleanly indeed,
and it's an excellent save.
Corner kick for Barce.
Ivan Rakatits to take it.
No chance to take a breath here as a ball
falls for Messi, but it
won't come down in time.
It's Rakatich who wins the header.
Ivan rakatitch again.
It's Danny Carverhal having a great game
for Real Madrid,
but the ball's been given away.
Tony Cross didn't realize that he had
a passer player right behind him.
No, it's Leo Messi.
Chance for Leo Messi.
Here his shot straight at Kayla Navas,
and it's blocked by the Costa Rican.
Now they've all fired up field
towards Cristiano Ronaldo.
Well, it's EndToEnd stuff here
at the Santiago Bernabette.
This second half took a little time
to get started,
but the last few minutes have been
enthralling, matching the first half,
which was excellent.
Substitution now for Real Madrid.
And it's an intelligent one, I think,
from Zidadin Zidane Casamiro,
who's on a yellow card is making way.
He's going to be replaced by Kovacic
with a change two
for Football Club Barcelona.
Pakwell Kappa has been taken off
and replaced by Andre Gomez.
This says Giroberto Suarez.
Yvonne rakatich pull back with Madrid.
Modrich not a bad pass from Luca Modrich.
But it's Testagon who gets there ahead
of Christiana Ronaldo and puts the ball
out of play for a Real Madrid throw.
Luca Modrich.
Once again to Ronaldo.
Now it's a Cencio,
the atmosphere building here
in the Santiago burner belt.
Marcelo puts across in towards the back
post where Ronaldo was waiting.
Messi into rocketitch now.
Jerry PK.
We find Samuel City.
Tidy football from Bastard as
they build slowly from the back.
Now it's with Andreagomez.
He finds Andres sIniesta.
Andrea Gomez drags his cross back,
but he can only pick out Nacho.
And he clears for Real Madrid.
Excellent challenge from Liam Messi,
although the ball immediately back
with Real Madrid and saysio in space,
on the far side, Marco Essencio.
Still with Marco Essencio,
whose left footed strike is very
well saved by Marc Andre Testegan.
Well, he went for the near post,
tried to surprise the German goalkeeper,
but Stegan well and true
and equal to it's.
A Belgian atmosphere here
at the Santiago Bernabel.
And this is a really good
result for Real Madrid.
In fairness, Barcelona really
need to win this one better.
Put pressure on Zidane side
at the top of the table.
Real Madrid already with a threepoint
advantage, don't forget.
Plus that game in hand
against Delta here's.
Messy just edging his way into the area.
Now it's Rakatic who strikes
one left foot in a hole.
What a goal that is by Ivan Rakatic.
An absolute stunner to put Barcelona into
the lead here at the Santiago Bernabel.
It's his 7th league goal of the season,
but he won't have scored many
more important than that one.
Ivan Rakatic rifles a left footed drive
into the top corner beyond Caleb Navas
and into the back of the net.
What a strike that is.
Brilliant from Rakatic as
he buries it to make it.
Real Madrid one.
Football club Barcelona two.
And it's a goal which momentarily
moves Barcelona level on points.
With Real Madrid at the top of the table,
it could prove to be a huge, huge goal.
And three massive points
for Football Club Barcelona.
There's still a long way to go.
Over 15 minutes remaining of this game.
But Real Madrid, after taking the lead
and now staring defeat in the face,
barcelo have managed to turn it round
here at the Santiago Bernabeau.
And after Casamiro's goal strikes
from Messi and Ivan Rakatic.
Make it.
Real Madrid, one, basset, two,
with 73 minutes on the clock,
score two stunning goals in this game.
Two goals worthy of victory in any match.
There's the corners
played in by Tony Cross.
Comes out to Luca Modrich who's
going to put it back into the mix.
It's headed clear by Jrpk.
And it's a throw in for Real Madrid
on the far sides.
What's a goal that was from Ivan Rakatic.
Such a sweet strike with his left foot.
He won't have scored many better or more
important than that,
Fernaldo has a go from the edge of the
area, and it's gathered by Tess Dagan.
Momentary panic for Barcelors.
There are a few white
shirts in space here.
It looked like offside to me.
Bentamar surely in an offside position
when he tested that one down
and played it back into Ronaldo.
Here's Messi into the gold score.
Ivan Rakatich.
Here comes Leo Messi.
Can't get the better of Marcelo.
And it's back with Real Madrid Tony Cruz.
And now it's Ascensio.
He's looked good since
he came on Marco Censio.
Although he gives the ball away, there
is Modrich Tony cross into Covisitch.
It's nacho now.
Marcelo.
Real Madrid, of course,
is desperate to win La Liga.
They haven't won it since 2012.
Suarez can't keep it on the far side.
It's a throw in for Nacho.
Excellent pass from Tony Cross
into Carrie Bentamar.
Bentamar place the ball
into the area towards Marco.
OCEANEs out by Jared PK.
It's a really poor
challenge and a late one.
Oh, it's a straight red for Circuit Ramos.
It's a straight red card for Circuit Ramos
for a late challenge on Leo Messi.
Well, I have to say
it was a poor challenge,
but I never thought it was a red.
Well, it's another red card
for Serkio Ramos, who certainly
cleaned his act up in recent seasons.
But this was something we saw over
and over again a few years back.
He catches Leo Messi very, very late here.
Wow.
Actually, I'll tell you what,
he goes in twofooted.
It's a twofooted lunch.
It's a stupid challenge
from Circuit Ramos.
Well, that's a red card.
It's a twofooted lunge from Circuit Ramos.
What was he thinking?
It's a ridiculous challenge
from the realm of your captain.
It looks worse every time you see it.
And I think the referee's got
that one absolutely right.
Well,
sarcastic, ironic applause from Ramos
as he leaves the field of play,
which is exactly what we saw from Neymar,
which is why he's missing this game.
So that could be a threemonth
fan for Circuit Ramos or more.
Well, that really changes things.
Real Madrid with ten men
on the verge of losing El Classico against
Bastard, and potentially without their
captain, Serkio Ramos, for maybe
three or four out of eager games.
It's put out a play by Kovacic.
It's a corner for Football Club Barcelona.
And things are suddenly very, very
different here at the Santiago Bernabeau.
And it's mainly because of this rifle
of a strike
from Ivan Rakatitch, which turned the
tables here, which put Bastard in front.
And after that,
Serkio Ramos literally saw red.
He's been given his marching orders
for a twofooted lunge on Leo Messi.
What a stupid challenge it was
from the Real Madrid captain.
And maybe, just maybe,
the pendulum
has swung slightly in favor of Barcelona
in terms of the league title.
Andre Gomez gets his cross,
and it's Jerry PK.
Fantastic save from Kayla Navas.
An unbelievable opportunity there
for Jerry PK to make it three
one to Football Club Barcelona.
His shot.
Charged down by Kayla Navas.
What chance this was.
Andrea Urmist does brilliantly well.
Plays a one two with Suarez.
He then picks out Jerry PK,
who can't find the back of the net.
Superb goalkeeping from Kayla Navas,
who smothered that one.
At the other end is
Cristiano Ronaldo with a shot.
Hummus about to come on for Real Madrid,
determined to get back into this game.
And here comes Leo Messi,
where it's three against two.
And it's Kovacic who's going to go
straight into the book for a really
poor challenge on Messi.
There's no question
that that's a yellow card.
The Real Madrid players
complaining about it.
It's a professional foul.
He's got nowhere near the ball.
It's a lunge on Messi,
and it's quite clearly a yellow card.
And he stopped Football Club Barcelona
from what was potentially
a three against two.
It could have quite easily
been the third goal.
At the other end, ronaldo was complaining.
He thought this should have been a corner.
And quite rightly, it should have been.
The ball evidently coming off Jerry PK
and going out for what should
have been a corner kick.
The linesman missed it.
So chitted the referee
and awarded Real Madrid.
Bastard.
The goal kick, Karen Bentamara,
has been replaced by Hammers Rodriguez.
By the way, here comes in yesterday,
picked up by Kovacic.
Now.
It's Marcelo.
Eight and a half minutes of normal time
remaining here at the Santiago Bernabel.
So far, so good for football.
Club Barcelona.
It's round trip one, Bastard two.
What a game.
Best classic ofer a long, long time.
Real Madrid
are also playing the remaining minutes
here with ten men after Serkio Ramos was
set off for a twofooted
lunge on Leo Messi.
Here comes Messi.
Messi strike.
It's another good save by Kayla Navas.
It's out for a Barcer throw.
What's a result this would be for Bastard
taking short.
It's picked up by Covassits, though.
For Real Madrid.
Put straight out of plate.
There was too much pressure on him.
Three bastard players around him.
It's a throw in taken by Sergio Roberto.
Here's Ivan Rakatitch
very much the hero here.
What a performance from Ivan Rakatitch,
and what a goal,
which could turn out to be the winner.
Seven minutes of normal time remaining.
We've had 83 here
at the Santiago Burnobel.
Real Madrid are the kings of late goals,
but they're down to ten men hit.
Rakatic with the free kick.
It's Jeroffee K who wins.
The header at the far post.
He's a chance here for a realm,
which leads to counterattack.
Cristiano Ronaldo.
He's got Marcelo outside
him and finds him.
Marcelo's first time ball over to the far
side is going to be picked up by Hames
Hamas, the substitute for Real Madrid,
coming on for Karen Bensomar.
Finds Danny Carverhalli.
He's been absolutely everywhere.
The Spain pullback,
and it's Hamas who strikes one.
Straight into the gloves of marc
Andre Terstegen
took a deflection, which actually made
things easier for Terstegan in the end.
Took the sting out of the shot.
And yes, they're beaten
to the ball by Luca Modrich.
So round with your throat.
His covisitch for Real Madrid finds
his compatriot, Luca Modrich.
Now it's Hamas.
To Carverhal back into Hamas.
Rodriguez he finds Tony Cross.
Cross into Marcello.
A good field up this from football
club from Real Madrid.
And the ball in and is converted by Hamas.
Well, well,
with their backs against the wall,
real Madrid have managed with ten
men to get back into this game.
And it's inspired the substitution
from Zidane because it's Hames who's been
on the pitch for only a couple of minutes,
who made the nipos run and has made it two
two hit with just five minutes remaining.
Would you believe it?
Real Madrid with another late goal.
And that could be decisive
in terms of the league title.
It's played in by Marcelo
to the near post.
And it's Hames who gets there
ahead of Serkio boost gets and on this
occasion, there's absolutely nothing
that Mark Angela Tersenegan can do.
It's a really good finish from Hames.
An excellent ball in from Marcelo,
and just as it looked at
Barcelona, we're going to be on top here
and take a big step towards potentially
winning the league of title.
Real Madrid have managed to get back
into the game with just ten
men on the field of play.
And here comes Asncio once more.
Marco Essentio.
It's cristiano Ronaldo into hames.
Hammes crosses the ball for ASENCIO,
goes for gold himself the second time.
And it's saved to buy Terse degen.
What a game.
Well, it doesn't look like being
the result that Barcelona perhaps deserve
in this game,
but it has been such an entertaining game
of football
best classic for quite some time.
It's totally lived up to its billing
as the biggest game on the planet.
There have been chances at both ends
for both sides,
and Barcer now have three minutes
to try and win this match.
A win they so desperately need.
A win that would put them level
with Real Madrid at the top of the table,
despite the fact that the whites
do have a game in hand.
They've got some tricky games
coming up, though real Madrid.
That game in hand, of course, is away at
Seltzide, who, like Madrid, are through to
the semifinals of European competition.
Seltzer through to the semis to play
Manchester United
in the Europa League realm.
Madrid, of course,
through to the semis to play
Athletico Madrid in the Champions League.
They've also got to play Valencia
at home, severe at home.
Malaga away.
Next game is against
Deport away from home.
So some tough games coming up
for the whites as Marcelo tries to keep
this one in Anthuns, but it's picked up
by two at a second faster fixture list.
Certainly more appetizing
than Real Madrid.
Certainly.
On paper, at least, slightly easier.
They've got Oscissuna at home next week.
Then it's away against Espanol at home
to Viral, away at last, Palmas,
and then ending the season
with a home game against Abar.
Here's Marco, I Sentio for Real Madrid,
taking on Jerry PK, getting a shot away as
well, and it's a good
save from Terse Tegan.
How many times have we said
that in this game, Marco?
Osenio's cross picks out Ronaldo.
He can't get a shot on target.
And it's a goal kick
for football club Barcelona.
And well, against all odds,
it's Real Madrid who are
finishing this game on top.
They're down to ten men.
Don't forget,
you wouldn't know it, though.
Rakatic inside.
To Andres iniesta.
Is there one final twist in this match?
We're in the final minute of the 90th.
Jordy alba into serkio brusquettes.
Not the best pass from Busquets.
He was looking for Messi,
but it's headed down by Marcelo
into the path of Caylon AVAs, and picked
up now by the realm of goalkeeper.
Going to be only two minutes of additional
time at the end of this game.
Parcel, I'm sure, would have been
hoping for at least three or four.
Jordy Alba tried to square it for Suarez.
It's been robbed by Luka Modric
and his hammers.
He cuts inside.
I'm gonna go miss.
And draws the foul.
It's a freekick for Real Madrid
and an opportunity for them
to waste some valuable seconds.
And the seconds do continue to kick
away here at the Santiago Bernardo.
We've almost had 1 minute
of additional time.
And it looks like this goal by Hames.
He makes a brilliant run to the near post.
He's not picked up by anyone.
It's a really good finish as well,
where it's heartbreaking for Basa,
who got back into the game,
got themselves in front,
were playing against ten men,
and we're surely thinking
that the points were in the bag.
30 seconds remaining here
at the Santiago Bernabel.
Here.
Come Barcelo.
Could this be their final
attack of the game?
It's Sergio Roberto who's
bringing it forward now.
It's Andrea Gomez.
He's got Jordy Albert outside him.
Here is Jordy Albert.
Leo Messi.
Oh, he's done it.
Leo Mercy with what could be
the last kick of the game.
Buries it into the back of the net.
It's heartbreak for Real Madrid,
but it's jubilation for Bassa.
Well, they've done a Real Madrid.
They've scored a lastminute goal.
92 minutes are on the clock, and Bassa
have put themselves back in front.
And it's Leo Messi with his 500th Barcer
goal, his 23rd goal in El Classico,
and his 31st strike of the season.
Who makes it Real Madrid to Barcer three,
and is surely handed all three points
now to Football Club Barcelona.
It was Sergio Roberto who burst forward.
He found Andrea Gomez,
who did well to hold up the plate.
His pastor, Jordy Alba, was perfect.
He squared it for Leo Messi,
who just had to tuck it beyond
Caleb Navas and into the back of the net.
It was such a wellworth move
from Football Club Barcelona.
And it's a goal that has given football
Club Barcelona victory here
at the Santiago Bona Belt.
The final whistle has gone and this goal
from Leo Messi has handed
Barcelona all three points.
It's all square in La Liga.
Real Madrid and Barcelona
both have 75 points.
Madrid do have a game in hand,
but it's a game that they could
so easily lose away at Seltzer.
What a climax to this La Liga season.
Highly get.
There's no question
that the league title is there to be won.
After it's finished here at the Santiago,
bernabeu Rail will get two, three.